Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
Chitose Is Life
Hey, isn't that...
Chitose-chan!
I've been a huge fan ever since
I first heard your voice.
Thank you. That makes me really happy.
She's a goddess.
There's an angel here.
Chitose, we need to get going.
Oh, right. I'll see you on the stage.
Yeah!
Green Room A
Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
Karasuma Chitose-sama
I guess you're a real pro now.
Just who do you think I am?
Maybe you won't need my help anymore.
Don't say that, Gojo-kun.
If you don't continue to support me,
I don't know what I'll do.
Jeez...
You're the best little sister I could ask for.
Really?
Chi-chan, wake up already.
Jeez, Gojo-jun...
This isn't good. They're all staring over here.
You're embarrassing me...
What a fool.
She's a fool, but she's really a big deal.
A big fool.
Don't worry, Gojo-kun.
I won't fire you just yet.
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
Momoka Is Life
Green Room B
Kusure
Cast and Staff
Karasuma Chitose-sama
Sono Momoka-sama
Shibasaki Kazuha-sama
Kugayama Yae-sama
Katakura Koto-sama
All right, now that everyone's here...
#04 High-Spirited Chitose and Her Merry Friends
Everyone do your best at the episode 1
early-screening-type event!
So... What's she doing over there?
She's reflecting. Please don't mind her.
Gojo-kun, you ogre, demon, manager.
So is the author really not showing up today?
Yes, he needs to work on his manuscript.
Right, right. Well, it's best
to strike when the iron's hot.
We need him to write lots,
sell big, and become happy.
Chi-chan, you can sit here.
Oh, Yae. You're a true friend.
That Gojo-kun is so mean.
How dare he punish his cute
little sister in this day and age?
Maybe he actually has a sister complex.
That'd be really annoying.
You really amaze me with how
optimistic you can be, Chitose.
But I totally understand how Chi-sama feels.
I was so nervous last night
that I couldn't sleep well.
Me, too. This is pretty nerve-wracking.
Huh? Is there something to be nervous about?
Huh? Then why were you just asleep?
We're singing the 90-second version
of the opening song today, right?
I really wasn't happy with what we recorded.
But we're singing it live,
so I practiced, of course.
All night, singing the full version on my own.
Ch-Chi-chan, that's amazing!
I always try to push my own limits.
It's tough when you're aware of
the fact that you're a professional.
Wouldn't staying up all night
before an event prove that
you actually lack any awareness
of being a professional?
Well, it's not like the song's that hard, either.
Can you do the full version, Shibasaki?
If I only have to sing.
Huh...
I should have practiced more.
It's still nerve-wracking,
no matter how much you practice.
Well, I mean,
today's a screening,
so as long as we have the anime,
it really won't matter if we flub up a little.
You think so?
Sure.
So a little nap won't hurt anything.
Heyo.
Hm? That happened after all?
I see. Well, that's not good.
What about the streaming?
Uh-huh.
Okay, okay.
Then it'll all work out,
with no Nyarlathotep chaos.
Well, mistakes in a live concert
just make it feel more "live," right?
Hey, got a sec?
Oh, sure.
Not that I'd know.
So, you see...
I have good news and bad news.
Which do you wanna hear first?
Whichever will make this go quicker.
All right, I'll go in order.
So we planned for them to sing
the opening song today, right?
How are they doing?
You think they're good to go?
I think my three are the same as usual.
Well, that's great.
It looks like we might end up
with some extra stage time.
So why don't we go all-out
and have them sing the full version of the song?
Huh?
Er... I mean, didn't we discuss
that it'd only be the TV-size?
Well, I mean, they were just talking about it...
Green
Tea
Momoka-chan, Kazuha-chan, and uh...
um... Ch-Chitose whatever-chan...
Her name is Karasuma Chitose.
Please Throw Away
Bento Box Trash Here
Tea, PET Bottle Trashbin
Right! Chitose Karasuma.
I totally heard her say she
could sing the full version.
But...
Reception
And!
It's just been decided that we're going to
be streaming this live! Boom-ba-da-boom!
Wha— I wasn't told about that...
Well, it just dawned on me.
We have this opportunity,
so we need to go all-out!
For the sake of the world, the fans,
and most of all, for those girls!
You'll have to check with
the other managers, too...
So what's the good news?
Huh?
That was the good news!
This gives them an even bigger
chance to boom, show their appeal,
and their fans will increase like boom!
Then that'll double, and boom!
They'll rise to the top in the star derby! Right?
So... What's the bad news?
Sorry! So sorry! Looks like they couldn't
finish episode 1 in time, after all!
What?!
Well, it'll be done in time for
the broadcast, so don't worry.
Episode 1 Early Screening Event
So we're just going to be screening
the PV with bits and pieces of episode 1.
But isn't the audience expecting a
completed episode 1 from the series?
No, no. They're all fans of the cast,
so they'll be ecstatic, and it'll
be a win-win situation for us.
I'm going to go rearrange
stuff with the sound guys.
Towada, go ahead and let the
author's guys know about this.
Thanks!
So, um...
That's what's going on. I'm very sorry.
What?!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
I-Is everyone okay with this?
I'm definitely not.
I'm going to sing.
This is our job, so we have no choice but to sing.
But, but...
Now, now, my true friend.
I'll be sure to back you up.
I'm worried about you the most.
If you guys could go stand by now.
Okay!
Hey, hey, Gojo-kun. Aren't I amazing?
Why, exactly?
Well, I practiced that much yesterday,
and this happened today. It was totally worth it!
My chance to appeal to the
audience went up like bam!
And then I'll gain even more fans like ba-bam!
And I'll be racing straight down
the road to stardom! JK!
Anime Adaptation
Celebration Event
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
Anime Adaptation
Celebration Event
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
Anime Adaptation
Celebration Event
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
So, um...
Th-This is the first time we're
all singing together, isn't it?
What? Are you nervous?
No, no, no. Th-That's not it...
It's just...
Hey—
You'll get the hang of it in no time.
You seem brazen enough.
Eventually, you won't think a thing of it.
It's about time, so if you would...
Hello!
Hello.
He—
...llo...
Um...
Yes, I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Um... I'm already over the fact that they
didn't finish in time for the screening.
I had a feeling they wouldn't, anyway.
Oh, really?
How are things going right now?
We need them to at least send the storyboards,
or we won't even be able to conduct checks...
Oh, storyboards! Right, those things...
Yes...
What was going on with those...
I think they were just making
corrections toward the end.
Our amazing director's getting that done
right now, super fast. Super fast!
It's going to be like this
from the very first episode?
They should be just about done.
Why don't I give them a call?
Well, hey, no news is good news!
I'm counting on you... Seriously.
All right, it's about time for...
Oh?
Today's main event!
Take a look at our special footage!
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
Broadcast Begins This Summer
What the heck was that?
That was almost exactly like the PV.
What happened to episode 1?
Hey, isn't something wrong?
Don't you have the actual episode?
Where's episode 1?
Chi-sama?
Everyone! Are you all hyped up?!
I think it'd be nice if you guys
could get a little more excited.
But is that even possible?
Then I guess we'll have to show
you guys something special today!
Something special?
We're going to sing for you guys!
Come on, let's go, racing with the wind!
There's a rainbow-colored sunrise
That we're all waiting for
So let's head to the promised future
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Doesn't this song not really fit?
Isn't it great? I asked a friend to make it for me.
The feelings that I kept inside suddenly...
Man, aren't those girls amazing?
The crowd's completely hyped up!
Though they are fresh-picked, lively newbies.
Nah, they're doing amazing.
Which means...
I think this way of promoting stuff works!
Looks like it does!
Keep it going. Keep it going, eh?
Maybe I'll hold an
agency-sponsored event, too!
Great job, everyone!
Chi-chan! Thank you! Thank you!
You sure helped us out.
My heart wouldn't stop pounding.
Nah, it was just coincidence.
I ended up nervous, too.
You really are a little shit,
but your damn guts never cease to amaze me.
Hey, great job, you guys. Great job!
Chitose-chan, you really do have talent.
Really? I do?
And I'm talented for seeing that in you. JK!
The live stream was hyped up, too.
Everyone was gushing over how
cute you were, Chi-sama.
Oh, come on. Really?
For real! A producer never lies!
Oh, come on...
I just got another bright idea, Gojo-chan!
What is it now?
Since this was such a big success,
let's stream every month.
We'll film along with the after-recording
sessions and hype this up even more!
There you go with your sudden whims again...
No, no, I've been playing
with this idea for a while.
It's all about increasing
the exposure of a title.
We have to keep up the hype regularly.
But...
I want this project to succeed, no matter what.
Even if I have to go over the line.
You feel the same too, don't you, Gojo-chan?
I'll see if I can adjust the schedule.
Yuta @-yuutanet1928
Momoka and Kazuha totally made eye contact with each other while they
were talking and I got teary-eyed. Also when Chi-chan backed up Yaepon
while Katakura-san looked on really shows that they get along and I'm
nothing but thankful. I'll draw a report drawing later. Drawing skills nao
#KarasumaChitose
HashoiWAV @-takayukiina...
The newbie Kusure battle lineup was super strong and
actually managed to joke with my ultimate duo, Momoka-tan
and Kazuha-sama. I can totally support Miss Chitose
#KarasumaChitose
She's so cute... She's pretty...
Recommended... I love her...
Haruguchi You @-catlayp8
There are so many things I could say that I could die,
but for now, Karasuma Chitose-san was pretty.
#KarasumaChitose
Syanon @-syanon88
Chitose Karasuma-chan......
I'll remember you now......
#KarasumaChitose
Reinashii @-sosuebdt8
Yuna is so cute. Super, super cute. I couldn't remember
the voice actress's name but she's super cute.
#KarasumaChitose
Yukiken @-syanon88
The screening was amazing. I'm getting flashbacks of Chi-sama's song.
I've never felt this way at a screening before... Oh, also, destroy DDD Pro.
#KarasumaChitose  #DDDProduction
Yakinikumaru @-yakinikumaru
This was my first time seeing Chitose-chan,
but she's great. DDD Pro, you guys suck
#KarasumaChitose
Hekoheko @-syanon88
The girl who plays Yuna was super duper hot ☺ ☺ ☺
#KarasumaChitose
Hiyoko@Fukuoka Delicacy@...
Aren't all of the Kusure voice actresses
including the newbies cute???? Precious...
#KarasumaChitose
Pizza @-death
Real Yuna is so cute it hurts. Her voice is also cute it hurts,
or more like her voice fits her character so much it hurts. Anime hurts.
#KarasumaChitose
Nishi @-westside77
I'm not sure what the hell was up with that screening, but the
fact that Yuna's voice actress was cute was my only salvation
#KarasumaChitose
Nanami @nanami-sakuragaoka
Kusure!!! Screening!!!!! Was amazing!!!!!!!!
Kaito&Yuna&Nanaka&Mao&Yuzu&Ria!!!!!!!!!
All of them!!!!!!!!!!!!! Super awesome!!!!!!!!!
#KarasumaChitose   #KusureEvent
Zenigata Capybara @-aegeee...
I want to talk about this event more than anything else this century. Like how
Momoka-tan and Kazuha-chan look like they really get along in real life, when
Chi-sama came in and they all held hands... It really felt like the Kusure world
was real... I can't return to this world. If only the anime would never start
#Karasuma Chitose  #KusureEvent
Kotsuno @-ailatob
I can totally support Miss Chitose. Aren't all of the Kusure
voice actresses including the newbies cute???? Precious...
#KarasumaChitose
Kitashika @esgutws
If the girls were colors, Momoka-chan is definitely pink and Kazuha-sama
is definitely blue. I think Katakura-san would be green. Maybe orange
for Karasuma-san? Yae-chan could also be pink but then she'd be the
same. I wonder if it's on the official page. I don't think they're used to
events like this yet, so maybe I'll recommend it to them. Maybe I'll put
up a poll, too. Maybe white is also a possibility. I wonder what else...
#KarasumaChitose    #Kusure
Chi-sama, Chi-sama.
What?
Hey, are you free the day episode 1 airs?
We were thinking about watching
the first episode together at Koto-chan's place.
Yeah, I'll totally be there! I love stuff like that!
Great job.
I'll be leaving now.
So...
Why don't the three of us live-tweet?
Good idea! That sounds like
something a voice actor would do.
We've been voice actors
for quite a while now...
Oh, right! So we're super popular voice actors!
Uh, I didn't say that.
Oh, come on.
What?
Hopefully we'll be popular someday.
You seem dissatisfied.
I'm not dissatisfied.
I'm just disappointed in myself.
But the crowd loved it.
True. Everything just seems so stupid.
Well, that's what they want
from us, so it's fine.
I'm glad the author didn't show up today.
We could never show him an event like this.
Maybe he didn't show up because
he knew this would happen.
Huh?
Well, considering the visuals
at the recording session...
You knew, too, didn't you?
Well, deceptive PVs happen all the time.
That's what my dad always says.
He may be right.
All right, I'm heading out, Gojo-kun.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Katakura-san's house, right?
You're going this late?
Yeah. They're having a Tanabata
festival at the shrine over there.
See you later!
Takoyaki
Sorry I'm late!
We just got here, too.
Right?
What's wrong, Yae?
Well, I was just thinking I haven't met up
with anyone at a festival since grade school.
I'm grateful that I became a voice actress.
That's a bit overboard.
Does that have anything to
do with being a voice actor?
Man, this sure takes me back.
Do you want to write a wish?
Sounds great. I heard
this shrine is pretty blessed.
Do Tanabata and shrines have
anything to do with each other?
Or is it just a bandwagon thing?
Hey, what wish did you two write?
That the animation will be
amazing and move smoothly.
I wished for everyone to have fun.
Cheap.
I mean the paper quality.
I-I see... What did you write, Chi-chan?
The same as you two.
Come on. Let's get going.
Lessen
the agency's
margin!
Th-Thanks for having us.
I live on my own.
You don't have to be so modest.
Okay...
I haven't been to someone's house
since I was in preschool.
I'm so happy that I became a voice actress.
We can talk the night away.
This place is pretty tidy.
Really? I'm pretty picky
about the merchandise I get.
This place may look clean,
but you can't fool the eyes
of this master detective.
Huh? Wait, that's weird...
I can't believe you actually are tidy.
This is unforgivable!
Hey, don't!
I have a feeling I know how
Chi-chan tidies up now.
I don't do it. Gojo-kun just cleans
everything without asking.
You actually have your brother
clean up your room for you?
Oh, don't worry about that.
I think it's just a reply notification.
Oh, right. I should tweet something, too.
I'm still not too sure when I should comment...
Really?
Yakinikumaru @-yakinikumaru
@karasuma_kaaaaa
I'm also waiting seiza style!
#Kusure
Chi-chan, do you reply to all of those?
Nanami @nanami-sakuragaoka
@karasuma_kaaaaa
The day is finally here! Are you and Katakura-san friends?!?!?!
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
@nanami_sakuragaoka
We're really good friends~(^o^)
#Kusure
That's commendable. I'm surprised
you're able to do that.
Zenigata Capybara @-aegeee...
@karasuma_kaaaaa so cute
#KarasumaChitose   #Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
@igodaisui-fm Thanks!
#Kusure
Pizza @-death
@karasuma_kaaaaa
I'm jealous lololol
I wanna join too lololololol
#Kusure
Well, it's important to treasure your fans.
You're such a pro.
Nah, it's not a big deal.
Horikita Yui
Tweets                  Following                 Followers
Well, anyway, let's check out our anime.
Notifications
News
Messages
Profile
Karasuma Chitose
Tweets                  Following                 Followers
If I round up twice, I have five digits, too...
Hopefully the visuals look fun.
Yeah. I wonder how everyone will react.
Equal? No, I surpassed her!
Bakugeki C's Magazine Editing Department
Huh? Isn't Kusure on today?
Yeah...
"Yeah"?
Shouldn't you be doing
a screening with the author?
It's fine.
I never got a reply about the storyboards,
and we just barely got
the white box this morning.
R's Comic
TV Anime Broadcast Starting!!
Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
I see...
I went to Kadokura-sensei's place,
and we both watched it,
so it's fine.
That's rather vague.
Bakugeki C's Magazine Editing Department
Sensei doesn't have very many friends,
so we need to make this a bigger deal...
It's fine.
He said so, too.
Hey, it's starting.
My song... My song's coming up!
I'm getting nervous!
Yae @yae-pon-poko
Eep, it's finally time (*_*)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Sorry to keep you waiting!!!!!
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
Standing by
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
@-katakurakoto Hype!
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
@karasuma-kaaaaa
You're good, but you're annoying...
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
We're going to keep talking to each other like this, so follow us!!!!!
#Kusure
Yae @yae-pon-poko
I'm getting super excited (*_*)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
it's coming...
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
Oh, no! My hands are shaking!
#Kusure
Yae @yae-pon-poko
@-katakurakoto
Me, too (*_*)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Chomp, chomp, shake, shake!
#Kusure
It's pretty unique from the opening, so I can't wait to see how
the animation turns out! I learned direction could also look
like this so I learned a lot on scene. Please check it out!
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
@-katakurakoto
Summary: Beware of goosebumps!!!!!
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
Would you not summarize!?
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
But I really learned a lot! But I think I finally see the shape of the acting
that I should pursue, or like, my own acting plan and the direction
worked together and created chemistry. Because of that, I got to
personally see an anime be born right in front of my eyes and I have
nothing but thanks and respect!  I'll keep working diligently!
#Kusure
Yae @yae-pon-poko
You two sure type fast......#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaah!
#Kusure
Yae @yae-pon-poko
@karasuma-kaaaaa
You drank too much (*_*)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
@yae-pon-poko What the hell?
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
#Kusure
Koto @katakurakoto
@karasuma-kaaaaa
Chi-sama, you're way too annoying (lol)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah it's still the commercials
Kusure
Yae @yae-ponpoko
@karasuma-kaaaaa
Let's just calm down and watch (*_*)
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaah Ah Ah Ah
#Kusure
Koto @-katakurakoto
it's starting!
#Kusure
Yae @yae-pon-poko
Awa
#Kusure
Chitose @karasuma-kaaaaa
Oh
#Kusure
Wait, are we going to travel
at the speed of light?
No way... Our bodies won't hold up.
This is the only way.
Circular Ouroboros that dwells in nothingness,
lend me your strength!
Um... Is this...
Don't say any more.
Jeez!
K-Koto-chan...
There's no way we could win with that!
Are they stupid?
Are they stupid? Are they stupid?
I can't help but think that.
But I'm sure everyone's doing their best...
"Chitose's cute."
"I like the girl who plays Yuna."
Ryunosuke @-ounapor 1023
Only watching Kusure this season.
Have faith in our Chitose-chan.
#KarasumaChitose   #Kusure
Nishi @-westside77
My God, the animation's awful.
But Yuna's cute, so I can forgive that.
#Kusure
Nishi @-westside77
You okay? Might job change from being a Momoka fan.
I wanna support the next voice actress from a series that bombs.
#KarasumaChitose   #Kusure
Zenigata Capybara @-aegeee...
Chi-sama is an acting god
#KarasumaChitose   #Kusure
Pizza @-death
Chi-chan is cute. That's enough to make me happy.
#Kusure
Followers
It's basically looking like
I'm a popular voice actress,
and the opening single will be out soon, too...
Overall, it's slightly a plus. Sort of.
Continuing our previous discussion...
Oh, about what's next for those girls?
Yes, yes.
Let's go ahead and make this
an even bigger project.
How about we go for a next-generation,
large-scale audition?
And then we can have them
announce their CD debut at an event
sponsored by Number One Production.
Then we can discover and
nurture a ton of golden eggs.
Great! That sounds great!
You totally found the method behind winning.
Let's make sure we pick up
all that loose change.
Now, now. My job is to give them opportunities,
and it's the girls' job to go pick all that up.
They're the stars.
I just work behind the scenes.
Huzzah! That's our capable producer!
You're the man who sells
pickaxes during the gold rush!
Next Time
Millennium Princess x
Kowloon Overlord
"I'm the One Who Wants to Cry"
You've dug it up.
Preview
You've been living on your
own for a while, Koto-chan?
Yeah, I've lived on my own
ever since I moved to Tokyo.
I always dreamed of living on my own.
A lot of voice actors still live at home.
That might be.
And there are a lot who live with a younger
brother or a younger-brother-type, too.
Hey, hold on a sec. Don't say stuff like that.
Saying "younger-brother-types"
will just cause misunderstandings.
Wait, what misunderstandings?
Well, they're just unfounded rumors, but...
Oh! That's why Chi-chan lives with her brother...
Huh? Wait, no, no! That's not it!
I don't like my brother at all!