Now for this week's hits chart...
Start the countdown!
Our Lost Ballad
Rainbow Sunrise
Did you see, Годзё-кун?
As of this week, we've shipped out
an estimated 10,000 copies!
I'm so good!
Whose estimate is that?
It doesn't mean you did a good job.
It means the people who
wrote the song did a good job.
Годзё-кун, I'm a pro, too.
I totally understand that.
I hope so.
The Ghost Kitten Connection
Playing
By the way, what I have here is...
Ta-da! The drama CD starring the
genius voice actor, Карасума Годзё!
The Ghost Kitten Connection
Playing
Its sales figures are immeasurable.
You actually have that?
Avenging you with a force of 10,000
since the times weren't on your side...
Who's the sister who cares
that much about her brother?
Me!
Годзё-кун, Годзё-кун.
See? I'm great, aren't I?
Episode 5 airs later today.
You Пареньs aren't meeting up again?
We've been replying back
and forth, so it's fine.
We just need to look like we
get along to people online.
You haven't even been watching
it on air lately, have you?
Годзё-кун, I told you that I'm a pro, didn't I?
I know most of the story
from the recording sessions.
If I watch my timeline and say things
in line with what's being said, I'm fine.
You really are trash.
#05 Cocky Титосэ and Shattered Popularity
Cast: Юна (CV: Карасума Титосэ), Нанака (CV : Сибасаки Кадзуха),
Mao (CV: Кугаяма Яэ), Yuzu (CV: Соно Момока), Ria (CV: Катакура Кото)
(CV: Карасума Титосэ)
A great song, great lyrics, and a great me.
Ти-тян.
Oh! I'm sorry! I'm off the clock,
and I'm heading to a recording session,
so if you'd like an autograph,
please go through my agency.
If you'd like a handshake,
there's a limit of one per person.
Oh, it's just you two.
You really are amusing, Ти-сама.
Were you curious about it, too?
Curious?
You know, about how popular our
series is or what the shops look like.
Right! Congrats to us for getting 10,000! Yay!
Yay.
Let's see... The single costs
1,400 yen without tax,
multiply the percentage...
click, click, lick, lick...
Aww... I should have gone for royalties
instead of taking a lump sum!
Ch-Ти-тян! Don't write on my hand!
Maybe it's not doing well, after all...
Ти-тян?
Яэ, where are your sunglasses?
Huh? But it's not that bright out...
That's not what I mean. You need
to make sure you're not recognized.
Act more professional.
Do people even know us that well?
We're voice actresses
who've sold 10,000 copies.
You never know when people are watching us.
Hey, isn't that...
See?
It really feels like we just
suddenly got super popular.
Hey, I knew it.
You think so?
It's the girl from the commercial!
At this rate, we'll be singing at the
Budokan by the end of the year!
You really think so?
JK. I'm just kidding. Come on, let's go.
It's our super fun work time!
Er, right...
Кото-тян, what's wrong?
A voice actress who's sold 10,000
copies shouldn't look like that.
Yeah, but considering how the
most important thing looks...
Most important thing?
The anime itself.
By "anime," you mean...
Y-You idiot! G-Get out!
And there's the show everyone's
talking about this season.
You want to drop it by the start of the OP,
right? I saw that on a portal site.
This is hilarious. That poor Авторor.
But the original story is crap too, right?
I haven't read it, but I saw
that on a portal site.
Right.
Actually, I feel bad for the
voice actors on this series.
But the voice actors are crap too, right?
I haven't heard them,
but I saw that on a portal site.
Right. Who was the lead again?
We worked so hard...
I wish they'd try to see more of the good parts.
Yeah, but there probably isn't much
anyone can do when it looks like that.
Кото-тян, did you see the newest episode?
That was another piece of work...
I'm really thankful that we
got to be in an anime, but...
I was so happy, I practiced over and over
and worked hard at the
recording sessions, too.
And yet, look how it turned out.
It's so stupid.
But I still end up watching it.
I just can't bring myself to hate it.
Yeah, it's really stupid.
All right, let's change things up!
Our CD sold well, so it's like we basically won!
You think so?
Let's get our next jobs as
10,000-copy voice actors!
ODD Production
Harukaze Pictures
DDD Production
We'll use this as a stepping stone
to fly onto our next stage!
Yeah!
Y-Yeah...
All right, we got it. That's a wrap.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Yep!
What's wrong?
That was the end of the first cour, right?
Yeah.
What were they even trying to
accomplish with this story?
Who knows?
I was lost right through to the end.
Yeah, and we never had
any decent visuals, either.
Great job, Пареньs!
You, too.
So... We finally hit 10,000 copies! We did it!
Uh, thanks?
What are you talking about?
Huh? The opening song...
The opening song... I'm sorry. For what title?
What title? This one.
Oh, right. This is the only series
I'm working with you on right now.
I sort of got them mixed up.
I-I see.
We recorded that song a
long time ago, so I forgot.
So this is how top voice actresses act.
I think I got it.
Well, how much we sell is a matter of chance.
Don't dwell on it too much.
Just think about what's next.
Okay.
Well, well! Hello, everyone!
Since this was the last episode, the Авторor
of the original work brought you all a gift!
Sensei, go on.
Thank you very much...
Thank you, everyone.
Thanks to you, it turned into a wonderful anime...
Anime... What is anime?
We were able to make such a wonderful
anime thanks to all of you. Right?
Yep! Thank you very much!
He seems so down...
And I couldn't hear a word he said.
Man, it's finally over.
A lot happened, but I think we all did our best.
R-Right...
So let's celebrate to the fullest!
I wonder if we'll get yummy meat
again, or maybe fish this time.
Are you sure we can't get some
time to talk to the director?
He's working behind schedule now.
So far behind, he's working
double-trouble-time!
I see... I really wanted to
speak with him in person,
but as I mentioned before,
the direction of the last episode was
a bit different from the original story...
I thought that, too.
But the key animation's
already starting to get done.
If we had to do corrections now...
Right, time has to take priority.
But the depiction of the
characters is quite different...
You're exactly right! I mean, we are
dealing with his original work, so...
But if we have to fix things, the last
episode will end up being a recap.
Right. That would be bad.
But... But speaking on behalf of the creator...
You're absolutely right!
But, but, our progress...
Right, right, right.
Ти-тян?
They were arguing about something.
Wh-Why?
Dunno. Probably about
how the anime turned out.
Ah...
It must be hard on the anime studio,
the Авторor, and the distributor.
Since we're all part of the same business,
we just have to make things better together.
I-Isn't it pretty presumptuous
of us to say that?
You're too naïve, Яэ!
Making humility a virtue
is how a student thinks.
Out in the real world, no matter how
important the person you're working with,
you have to think of them as your equal,
or you can't do good wor— Yow!
Any who can go to the after-party
should head there first.
Why did you do that, Годзё-кун?
Did I do something wrong?
Let's go.
DV! This is domestic violence!
Годзё-кун, your love is too heavy!
You need to make it lighter,
you sister lover!
Right, but...
All right... If you'll excuse me...
Um... Director?
Mm-hmm.
Кудзу-san was wondering if we
could Редактор the final storyboards...
Mm-hmm.
We've been releasing the
storyboards on schedule,
so I told him we'd need earlier notice, but...
Apparently, the creator side
is strongly requesting it.
Mm-hmm.
So the animation supervisor got mad
and said he was going to quit.
Mm-hmm.
Do you think you can handle it, sir?
Really?!
Mm-hmm.
I thought it might be
physically impossible, but...
Mm-hmm.
If I had to deal with that amount of work,
I would've passed out by now.
Mm-hmm.
You're amazing, sir...
S-Sir?
Mm-hmm.
Sir!
Anime 2nd Season
Confirmed!
You want to delay the release?
Don't be stupid.
We're having a fair to go along
with the comics and the spinoff.
There's a second season planned after a
break, too. Can't you work something out?
It appears Kadokura-sensei has sustained
quite a bit of damage from the anime,
and can't seem to face reality.
Damage, eh?
An Авторor whose work became an anime
and an Авторor who never has one...
Who do you think is more blessed?
Well, that's...
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
Light novels are always two for one!
You either die or get killed!
Anime 2nd Season
Confirmed!
16th Anniversary
AMN Bunko
So you have to do it even if it kills you!
In Use
62 Minutes Remaining
If we actually report all of this red,
everyone's going to be super pissed...
It'll be fine.
Кудзу-san...
Because of these mounting demands,
the initial cost slightly...
slightly, just somewhat,
had no choice but to take a turn for the worse...
Hmm...
Uh... So...
As for the actual figures, Towada will
report them, since he's in charge.
Huh?
Make everyone ooh and aah with the gold card.
The bill's going to the creator, anyway.
Ти-сама, you really love
innocently making up songs, huh?
Is it really okay for us to eat so much for free?
Yeah... If only we could contribute
to the sales a bit more...
Maybe we can find a way to help...
You're too naïve, Яэ.
Butting into other people's
business is how students think.
Out in the real world, you need to
separate yourself from others.
You think so?
That's just how things are when you're working.
By the way...
I wonder what they'll treat us to next.
Maybe it'll be sushi!
Yow!
How long are you gonna listen to that?
You've got your next job to do,
so get into work mode.
My next job? Did I have something lined up?
A handout event.
What's that?
The first volume Blu-ray celebration
event at the summer Comiket.
You're going to be handing out novelties
to people who preordered
and paid in advance.
Aww... What the heck?
Blu-ray...
Uh, sorry. What title were you referring to?
What title?
Oh, right. I guess the only thing
I've worked with you on was Kusure.
I might have gotten a bit mixed up.
With what? What else could
you possibly mix it up with?
It's been a while since I recorded that, too...
Man, it totally slipped my mind.
Well, how much we sell is a matter of chance.
Don't dwell on it too much.
Just think about the next thing.
Let's hurry up and get my next job, Годзё-кун!
Ow, ow, ow!
What are you doing, Годзё-кун?
Being violent to the voice actress
you're in charge of...
Do you not not not realize you're a professional?
Shut up. Don't underestimate
me, you damn newbie.
What novelties?
Autographed postcards.
No one's going to buy
the expensive Blu-rays just for that.
I feel like there's not not not
any point in an event like that.
Everyone's doing what they can.
This is your job, so take responsibility
for it until the end.
Right...
Kusure Voice Actress Handout Event
BD, DVD Preorder Extras
Момока-тян and Кадзуха-тян aren't coming?
I heard they're working another event.
Huh... Must be nice being super popular.
Hey, maybe that's the event over there.
Entrance
Wow... I doubt they'll even
get through all that today.
Hey, Годзё-кун, how many
people are coming here?
We've estimated about a hundred
and distributed numbered tickets.
But we'll also be live streaming this.
Huh? So that's replacing the usual radio format?
Right. Just like the screening
of the first episode.
Yay! I'm going to get praised again!
Gotta timeshift reserve this!
Th-Thank you very much!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Huh. I guess quite a few fans showed up.
Th-Thank you very much!
Thank you so much!
Thank you.
Ended
So many people came.
Some even said they enjoyed the series!
There were people who watched,
and so many who even bought the Blu-ray!
Maybe I was underestimating this.
We can't get discouraged!
Yeah! It's not over yet!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Hooray...
Well, I don't mind getting more fans.
Ти-тян?
Nothing! Let's get even more fans,
and become popular voice actresses!
Yep, yep.
I still have to greet some people,
so you can head home first.
Then maybe I won't be treated like crap.
Tales
of the Bizarre
Animal Times!
Special!
This is the popular corner
you've all been waiting for!
We'll be showing you footage of
bizarre creatures we've found
all over the world.
Official/ch
Live
Live Streaming
User
Live
Upcoming Live Broadcasts
Broadcast Live
Past Programs
Popularity
On Air
Official    Anime
Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
BD, DVD Preorder Extras Voice Actor Handout Event
Man, it feels great being able see
the results of all my hard work.
Working is great.
Huh?
First, we have this creature!
Director, you haven't been
home in a while, have you?
This is a bug that everyone knows about,
Mm-hmm.
but it actually doesn't have a mouth.
Isn't that rough?
Mm-hmm.
Of course there's no way it wouldn't be...
Let's just quit.
We can't. This is our job.
Director...
They only live to provide
Mm-hmm.
the continuation of life to the future.
Next up, we have the tardigrade.
Despite also being called "water bears,"
The Редакторor-in-chief said it'd be
difficult to delay the release.
their shape doesn't resemble a bear very much.
This creature has the ability to regenerate
in the most extreme of conditions!
But in my opinion,
if the anime is making you suffer that much...
Anime?
Wow! My work is going to be made into an anime?
S-Sensei?
Yay! It's like a dream!
My first anime series... I'm so happy.
I hope it gets made...
into a fun anime!
I see... An anime, huh?
Sensei...
Apparently, they are easy to squish.
There are still many more
bizarre creatures in the world!
I can't wait to see!
The female of this extremely
rare animal that lives in Australia
I want to go home...
doesn't help with the rearing of young at all.
Huh? Does that mean only the
males take care of the young?
That's correct.
Of course, that means
feeding them, making nests,
and warming up the eggs
are all jobs for the male.
Wow! That's amazing.
What do you want, Кудзу-san?
Sorry about the other day.
Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
But you are, right?
You say that, but you're mad, right?
I said I'm not mad!
See? You're mad!
I don't think anything of it.
It can't be helped.
I'm an employee of this company.
No matter how hard it is,
and no matter how much I suffer,
I still have to work. That's what a job is.
Let's go somewhere else. I have something
important to discuss with you.
But I've still got work left.
Just leave it!
Okay...
Not only that, it also takes care of the eggs
that the female made with another male.
Wow...
I'm home... Huh?
Годзё-кун...
What? What's wrong with you?
Th-This...
I really hate her.
Пареньs! Let's all stop bashing Карасума Amateur-san!
I'm better than her
Voice actors who think they're hot shit are gross
I'm never watching an anime with her in it again
She's a pro amateur lolololololol
This voice actress isn't bad for an amateur
Take that, Kadokura
Карасума Титосэ is a shit voice actress who only got this role because of Nan Pro's massive push
You can't just be good at events...
Incoming Spam
She's about the 7th cutest in class
Don't underestimate voice actors. Die, die, die!
Voice actress from a bombed series
Piece of trash with a big head
Low-level stiff acting
Her attitude is trash, so she's got nothing going for her
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick... ugh
Kusure: war criminal forever
These are pretty accurate...
There's no point in getting upset over these.
But, but...
We'll filter out comments next time,
so forget about the Internet.
More importantly, I got surveys from today.
There may be stuff about how you are
at these events that you can improve,
so make use of them.
No. I don't wanna read those.
I only wanna see the ones
that are praising me.
What are you talking about?
Why am I the only one getting bashed?
I didn't even do anything!
That's...
Годзё-кун, bye-bye. Goodnight.
That's because you're
the only one who's not doing anything...
Bashed on the Internet, grilled by the vendors,
and squeezed totally dry.
This is bad.
Well, yeah, this is bad...
Yes, it's bad.
If we do end up in the red,
I won't be able to use up all of the budget.
What?
But... but...
But fear not, Towada-кун!
I have a secret plan.
Preview
What's your secret plan, Кудзу-san?
When talking about promoting anime,
there's nothing else!
Whisper, whisper...
What? You're going to get in trouble!
But if I get in trouble,
I just need to trick them by smiling and
going "teehee," and have you apologize.
You're not fooling anyone... hm?
Wait, did I somehow end up
being the one in trouble?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Remember what I taught you before?
Do you still remember that day?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Oh, come on! What else? The time I
showed you how to write a formal apology!
A formal apology!