Кусурэ Earnings and Expenses
Proposed Broadcast Start: October 2016
Production Cost Duration (12 серии Total)
Production Costs: 192,000,000 yen (16,000,000 x 12 серии)
Original Story Charges: 2,400,000 (200,000 x 12 серии)
Promtional Costs: 12,000,000 (1,000,000 x 12 серии)
Overall Production Costs: 264,000,000 yen
Peitax Expenses: 60% (123,840,000 yen)
Production costs
Expenses collected from other companies (40%)
Promotional costs (revenue) (1,000,000 x 40% x 12 серии)
Promotional/Sponsor costs (expenses)
Retail BD (6,800 yen x RY20%)
Production fees (2%)
Retail DVD (6,000 yen x RY25%)
Production fees
Rentals (4,000 yen x RY35%)
Production fees (2%)
National Distribution
Окт. (4 серии)      Ноя. (4 серии)      Дек. (4 серии)      Янв.      Фев.      Мар.      Апр.      Май.
Кудзу-кун. Кудзу-кун!
Kobayashi:
Кудзу
Towada
Tominaga
Business trip!
Shooting footage for bonus materials.
Will be back after the weekend. I'm sorry.
Leaving early
Do you know where he went?
Uh... nope. Can't say I've heard anything.
Huh... I see.
It couldn't be... No, it couldn't be...
Кудзу-сан uploaded a photo
Caught some hotties! Gahaha! Okinawa rules (heart)
Okinawa rules!
Кудзу!
Персонал Members
Aloha!
Mensore, Okinawa!
Note: "Mensore" means "welcome" in the Okinawan dialect.
#06 Титосэ on the Beach
and the Budget That Won't Go Through
Shisa
Well, since we have a good view of the ocean,
let's go ahead and start this thing.
The camera's scary. The camera's scary.
What's with her? Did something happen?
W-Well...
Ти-сама must be pretty hurt
from that last stream...
Calm down, Титосэ. We're just
filming for bonus material.
There's no streaming.
B-Bonus material?
Th-Then no one's gonna
write any comments on it?
Nope.
I see. Bonus material...
That means only people who paid
for the release will see it.
That's an awful way of putting it,
but you're correct.
Then they're on my side.
They're on my side!
I win!
Yep, we win! And so...
Here you go.
But why Okinawa? Why swimsuits?
Come on, Ти-сама, why are you
being such a party pooper?
Right now, the users want to
know more about you Пареньs.
And that's why we're going to send
them your most private moments!
And that happens in Okinawa?
Haisai! You're correct! We won!
Note: "Haisai" is the masculine form of "hello" in the Okinawan dialect.
Pretty lady! Treasure of the islanders! We won!
Haitai! We won!
Note: "Haitai" is the feminine form of "hello" in the Okinawan dialect.
Won? We're actually losing, sales-wise...
It'll be okay. It'll be okay. It'll be okay...
Sacrifices must be made so the
anime can grow and develop...
It'll be okay. It'll be okay. It'll be okay...
Яэ, are you okay?
Not at all.
Not okay, huh?
There's nothing to worry about.
It'll all work out with makeup,
lighting, and angles.
Anything bad can just be cut out later.
Wow, you're really used to this.
To be honest, I'm not sure how
you're able to stay so calm.
Yeah.
Well, this is just another part of our job.
You sure are mentally gorgeous,
despite how scrawny you are.
Look, it's Nio-сама! Nio-сама's here!
And then there's...
What's this about swimsuits?
I was only told we'd have
some revealing outfits.
Er... That was what they told us,
but when we talked to them today,
they said there were some changes.
And everyone else seemed okay with it,
so it was hard for me to say anything...
Um... Pardon me.
I'm sorry for butting in,
but why don't we decide after
we check the footage?
Usually, we'd also say no to this,
but we agreed it'd be okay if she checked and
they cut out any parts she wasn't happy with.
Yeah, yeah. That's it!
I just couldn't say no. Кудзу-сан is so pushy...
Luckily, the swimsuits aren't asНадписьed,
so you could compromise and
make it so you can choose
the one you're willing to wear, Сибасаки-сан.
All the other girls are going
to pick their own, too.
Well, if you insist...
All Mine!
High Tension
Okay, cut!
Great job, everyone!
Did you take some photos so I can check?
Yeah.
So, how'd I look?
Huh? Yeah, I'm sure whatever's fine.
There must be more to say than that.
Like how cute I was or how super cute I was.
Nope. You look like you normally do.
Like I normally do... So I'm naturally cute?
Yeah, yeah. You're the cutest in the world.
That was vague.
How does it look?
Yeah, I look super cute.
We didn't ask that.
Hey, you're in this shot,
too, Сибасаки-сан. Look!
You're very strange.
Strange?!
Oh, um... I was just wondering
how you could be so confident.
Confident?
Confident...
I was wondering how you can look
like you're having so much fun...
Huh? Uh... I-Isn't it fun?
I think the photos look good.
Let me see, too!
Момока-тян, you look fairly cute, too!
You know just how to piss someone off, huh?
What an awful expression.
A huge room...
All right, let's drink! Beer! Beer!
Rafute! Rafute!
Beer! Beer!
Tebichi! Tebichi!
I'm going to pass.
I don't feel like it, either.
Oh, come on, now. Let's have a drink.
Oh, but Momocchi, you get root beer.
Why do you say that?
And Kazuha-сама, you get this.
Cheers!
Good work!
Okinawa is great!
Man, I'm glad we were able to use our budget.
And there were no problems with the shoot!
Yes, there were! There were lots!
Next time you pull something
like that, I'll kill you!
Hey, come on. No need for jokes like that.
It's not a joke...
Thank you so much.
You really helped us out this time.
Er, I didn't really do anything...
Seriously, you saved us.
Кудзу-сан really is trash, isn't he?
So just having someone decent
around... Seriously, I just...
Well, we both have it rough.
Who is it? Who is it?
Who's the ordinary Парень?
The places for encounters are limited,
but a light novel author isn't happening.
L-Light novel authors aren't ordinary Пареньs.
So you're saying they're beneath ordinary Пареньs?
N-No!
Anyone need more sake?
Thanks...
I guess you're the type that can drink
whatever, huh, Kazuha-сама?
I don't really care,
as long as I can get drunk.
But since you're here...
Oh, thanks.
I never thought we'd come
all the way to Okinawa.
I never thought I'd be doing
anything like this, either.
But this was my last chance,
so I'm actually happy about it.
You know, since I'm 26.
Right. Swimsuit shoots would be...
Not just that...
Work, too.
If I couldn't get a main role on my next try,
I was going to go back home.
And then maybe try getting married.
"The country is in ruins, yet the
mountains and rivers remain."
"My dreams may be ruined,
but I've still got my home," they say.
No one says that.
They don't, huh?
Were you told to come back home?
Neither my mom nor my dad said anything.
They weren't against me doing this job...
Though they didn't actually support me, either.
They only talk about the silliest stuff.
So I figured I needed to decide for myself.
You're very mature.
I know, right?
Older means wiser— Hey!
Who are you sayin' is almost thirty?
I mean, I am almost thirty, but...
And meddlesome.
Aren't I?
Hey, hey, Кото-тян-who's-almost-thirty, isn't there any more beer?
There's only Awamori left.
Huh? What'd you just say?
Then let's have Годзё-кун buy us more.
He's only useful at times like this.
Титосэ! You dun' understan' a thing!
Huh? Uh, right, I'm sorry.
What?
Both you and Момока dun' understan' a thing.
R-Right...
Сибасаки, your Yamagata
accent's coming out.
No, it's not!
It is..
Oh, a pillow fight? You're so young!
I've never seen one in real life.
Wanna do this? You wanna do this?
Take this, you prissy little rich girl!
Special move: Титосэ Attack!
So cruel!
Ch-Ти-тян, that's pretty underhanded...
Huh? But they did that to me all
the time back in high school...
I don't think so!
Why, you...
Whoa, wait!
Salt
Chinsuko
Кудзу-кун...
Yes...
You know...
I'm home.
Hey, Момока-тян, it's been a while.
Do you remember me?
Oh, from Pure Para...
Right! Wow, you've gotten so big.
Thanks...
He brought me the theatrical all-stars version.
I see...
Oh, yeah. I've been thinking about
the casting for Pure Para next year.
Interested, Момока-тян?
I was thinking of having Сакура-сан
appear as the boss character, too.
Like, having the mother of the
new Pure Para be the boss
so mother and daughter
can star in it together.
My, that's lovely. It's like a dream.
That's only if we could do it.
Of course you can. I mean,
you're Сакура-сан's daughter.
It's great that you have your
own acting talent, too.
Once I make up my mind,
it's pretty much a done deal.
I don't mind either way,
but it's up to the actors
to make their own decision.
Момока, you're a professional now.
You can choose for yourself.
We'll support your decision.
Thanks...
I've got an early start tomorrow,
so I'm going to bed.
"Musashi-seki, Tokyo, to Another World?!"
~A Lively Corporate Slave Life Starting From Minus~
Voice Actor Audition
G-Good morning.
Яэ! Haitai!
Ти-тян, good morning. You're here early.
Actually, you're late, Яэ.
You're up next.
A-ha! This must be what they call "island time."
You still feel like you're at a resort, don't you?
Th-That's not true...
My last job ran a little late.
Thank you very much!
Oh, please. You're an islander now, huh?
Stuck in the Яэyama Islands?
Oh, you're already here, Яэ-pon.
Годзё-сан's been pretty anxious.
Yeah, I somehow made it.
Kugayama-сан.
Y-Yes! O-Okay, I'm gonna go.
Okay, go for it.
It'll all work out!
Anyway, you took a pretty long time, Кото-тян.
Yeah, they ended up askin' me to try out
for some roles I wasn't tryin' for, too.
Yeah? Hey, once we're done,
why don't the three of us go get dinner?
At an Okinawan restaurant!
Sorry! I have another job after this,
so I have to leave right away.
I-I see. Nah, that's totally fine.
Come to think of it, I might
have to do other roles, too,
so I might take a while, too.
It's great to hear that.
Do your best, Ти-сама!
Right-o!
Okay, I guess I'll get to work, too.
Okay, that's good.
Huh?
I-It ended in an instant...
But, well... yeah.
I mean, I've had experience as a protagonist.
I'll be popular!
Hey, do I have an audition
for Pure Para right now?
Huh? No. Why?
Well, someone pretty high up
at Hokuei told me about it.
Apparently, my mom might be in it.
Huh...
So he asked me if I wanted to be in it, too.
So he chose you...
If that's the case, we might have
to adjust your work load a bit.
We may have to put your musical career on hold.
But your mom's been on Pure Para in the past,
so I'm sure it'd be huge if you two
appeared as mother and daughter.
It should be a great opportunity
for you as an actress.
What did your mom say?
She hasn't said anything.
My dad said I could do what I want, too.
Huh... And what do you want to do?
I don't know.
Congratulations
Big Hit
Pajama Ninja Tomomi
Now, if we could have Shakujii-сама
from Anipro Entertainment come up?
I've just been introduced, but I'm
Shakujii from Anipro Entertainment.
30,000 copies!
Hit-maker!
CEO!
Thank you. The reason this was
such a hit is because of all of you.
It's not much, but I'd like
Why do wrap parties always fall on the same day?
to start the prize drawing.
Титосэ, we're gonna head
to the Кусурэ wrap party.
Huh? Do I have to go?
Actually, you didn't have to come to this one.
You had a mob role here,
but you're a main character there.
Yeah, I guess you're right...
What's wrong?
Hey, the audition the other day...
Oh, that. They picked someone already.
You lost. Totally failed.
Tch. Political casting, eh?
Death to record companies.
It's your own lack of ability, dumbass.
Годзё-кун, do you think I could be in trouble?
So you've finally gained a sense of danger...
Well, yeah, I'd say you're in trouble.
Yeah. My luck totally sucks.
Actually, I'm pretty sure you
got this far on pure luck.
Yeah, I don't need jokes like that.
That wasn't a joke.
All right, next... We have a huge TV
from Anipro Entertainment.
Maybe I'll go get purified...
We're going to the next wrap party first.
Let's see... Pink 57.
Yes! Me, me! That's me!
Huh... I guess I'm lucky after all!
I won!
That's called being useless...
Wrap Party Venue
Please... There are plenty
of open seats up front,
so if the cast would, um... come up here?
There's still a bit of time before
we start, so please hang tight.
Good to see you, Ти-тян!
And Ти-сама arrives fashionably late.
More importantly, listen to this!
Huh? I can start? I see. Well...
I just won a TV at another wrap party!
I wonder what I'll win here.
Now, if we can get right to it, I'd like
People don't usually win those that often, right?
to start this wrap party.
First, let's have a toast.
Mother
Calling...
Call Ended
I heard that the author's
editor-in-chief is here...
I'm not sure.
The possibility seems low to begin with...
Now, then...
Producer Кудзу, from my company,
will be leading us in a toast.
You all did well bearing with the pain.
I'm moved! Cheers! Thats what I'd like to say,
but that might jinx us,
so I'd prefer to go with "total victory."
Everyone, do you have your glasses ready?
Now, then...
Total victory!
Cheers...
Right. Well, let's go right into
the introduction of the main Персонал.
Mother
Calling...
Your phone's ringing.
I know.
You don't need to answer it?
I'll call them back later.
I'm going to get another drink.
Thanks for all your hard work, Соно-сан.
U-Um... Would it be okay to get your autograph?
Oh, sure. That's totally fine.
Thank you, too.
Thank you very much!
Now I've got both yours and your mom's!
U-Um, I was doing key animation
on a project Соно Сакура-сан was in,
and she gave me her autograph
then. I was so happy!
Oh, I see!
I'm sure my mom will be
happy when I tell her that.
Total victory! Total victory!
Сибасаки never listens to a word I say...
Huh? There's no after-party?
That's not exactly rare.
There are some titles that
don't even do wrap parties.
Well, I know that the party is in full schwing...
Oops, I mean full swing!
You suck!
Well, there will be a second season,
so let's keep doing our best.
Thanks, everyone!
A second season, huh?
Even though the sales suck.
Yer gosh darn annoying!
Sales have nothin' to do with it!
"Gosh darn"... Where are you even from?
I dun fergot where I'm from!
Did you just drink too much and forget?
If I could drink, I'd like to forget, too.
Shut yer trap!
I know! I won't drink, and I can't drink.
You dun' get it at all... You can't ferget,
no matter how much you drink...
That's... That's why I keep drinkin'.
Yeah!
They're going to forget about this series, too!
Y-Яэ, are you okay?
There are lots of Ти-тянs...
There are lots of people to take
your place, too, Ти-тян...
Oh? I guess that's how you really feel, huh?
Яэ-pon, you drank too much.
You should rest a bit.
Most newbie voice actors are off all week...
This must be what Hell is like.
I'm gonna head out. Момока-тян, good job.
Let's go out to eat again sometime!
Титосэ! Your stop is Baba, right?
Hers is Ochiai, so I'll give you a ride.
Huh? Er, that's a bit...
I mean, if anyone saw us going home together
and started rumors, it'd be embarrassing...
Come on, let's go.
Yep. Gonna go home now.
Титосэ, hurry up.
Uh...
Great job, everyone!
Okay, I'd like to propose a toast to your eyes
to kick off this after-party.
Full of sun!
Well, we made it through this one.
Now let's do our best on the next one!
Right. I've been moving
that one thing along, as well.
Oh? How's that going?
Годзё-кун, do you have the documents?
Oh, yes, sir.
It's amazing. We're getting
auditions left and right.
Nice, nice. We won!
Uh, wait... What are we going to do
about the second season of Кусурэ?
Towada...
Yes?
Can I leave the rest to you?
Huh?
It's time for you to set off on your own!
I have nothing left to teach you.
Go! Walk over my dead body!
Corpse of the dead.
I think it's the series that just died...
Preview
Ти-тян's not here...
Yes, yes. Ти-сама went home.
We're goin' home, too.
Ти-тян's not in the next cour's cast,
or the cour after that...
Oh, crap. She's drunk. Definitely drunk.
Кото-тян, I'm sorry.
No worries. But it's strange
becoming friends with
someone who's so much younger than me.
Voice acting is such a wonderful job.
Friends?
What, we aren't?
No, it's just that I've never had
friends before, so I'm happy!
Huh? What about Ти-сама?
Well, Ти-тян's...