I tol' ya, it don' matter where ya came from.
What matters is where ya wanna go.
You just said that.
She's heavy in more than one way.
Shibasaki
Shibasaki, we're here. Do you have your key?
Key?
Key...
Nope.
Oh, dear, Kazu-chan.
Look at you, not answering your
phone and blubbering drunk!
Mom...
#07 Curious Chitose and Parents' Day
Oh? My, my, my!
I've seen you on that TV thing before!
TV?
Theory of Acting and Drama
Thank you for bringing her home.
Sorry for the trouble.
It's no problem.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
Of course I'd be surprised if you show up
on TV wearing a swimsuit like that.
Your father's very worried about you.
Were we on TV?
She probably meant the bonus footage.
Ah...
My grandma also calls any
kind of video footage "TV."
Wonderful, old-timey Japan.
Oh, dear.
Kazu-chan, where are your tea cups for guests?
I don't have any.
But what do you do when you have friends over?
Nothing. It's not like anyone comes over.
What am I going to do with you?
Come on. Your clothes will get wrinkled if you
don't change. Did you take off your makeup?
I'm sorry about all this.
Oh, don't mind us. We'll be leaving now.
Shibasaki-san doesn't have any friends?
You don't, either.
Well, yeah...
But that's not what I meant.
She's been like that ever since
she came here from Yamagata.
I see... Must be rough.
It's rough for everyone.
That's just how this industry is.
Right? So true.
My parents were against me
becoming a voice actress, too.
Oh, really?
I see... It's normal for parents to oppose that.
Yeah.
Well, Gojo-kun was also a voice actor, right?
We had seen some of the
harsh realities of it already,
so they tried even harder to discourage me.
Well, good work today.
Huh? Er... Huh?
Huh? My taxi fare...
After the jingle will be listener messages.
We've picked out some messages,
so please read them in order.
Okay!
Two, four, six, eight...
who do we appreciate...
We're gradually getting fewer messages.
The number of plays is also down.
Heyo! What's up?
It's rare for you to show up here.
I don't want to be in the office.
Then you should show up on site more often.
No, it's hard being there, too.
Hey, you've got a visitor.
Wha—
Who's that?
Excuse me for a moment.
What are you doing here?!
I went to say hello at your office,
and they asked if I wanted to come see you work.
Why would you do that?!
Well, your mom was worried
about your work, so...
Then you could have at least told me!
Well... Hello, hello, ma'am.
Please come over here so you can watch.
No, she'll be leaving right away.
Why, thank you, um...
He's the P of this series.
P?
He's the producer. Um...
You could say he's a very
important business partner.
I see.
That's wonderful for someone
who looks so young.
Oh, no... Well, you might say
this is a very merit-based business,
so age really means very little...
Hello. I'm the producer, Kuzu.
Thank you for taking such
good care of my daughter.
Hey—
For me? Thank you so much!
Towada, get her some tea. Some for me, too.
Hurry it up, now.
Sure.
Would you please just stop?
Kazu-chan, would you please
hand these out to everyone?
There's one for you, too.
This is embarrassing!
You're embarrassing me!
You've got a nice mom.
An Interview With Torimaru Chitose-san, Who Plays the Main
Heroine Yuna in "Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord"
It's not Torimaru.
Shibasaki-san's experiencing Parents'
Day at work right now lolololololol
Read
Work, damn it!
How is this a radio program? CooS Radio!
This program is brought to you by...
...Peitax Entertainment.
We've got all of the heroines here today.
Yae-chan, who plays Mao, and Koto-chan,
who plays Ria, are joining us today.
I'm Kugayama Yae, and I play Mao.
Th-Thank you for having me.
Good evening, everyone!
I'm Katakura Koto, and I play Ria.
Wow, the studio seems much
smaller with all of us here.
It feels so crowded.
Sorry Yae's taking up so much room.
Chi-chan, do you want to die?
Oh, man... It's only been five seconds,
and we already have to cut.
Obviously, we're going to have
to redo that from the top.
All right, here we go again from the top.
Five, four, three...
All right, next up is...
Listener messages!
We've got lots of messages again today.
Thanks, everyone!
Let's see... Kusure name,
"Chinese Fried Sesame Dumpling-san."
"CooS evening, everyone." Yes, CooS evening.
CooS evening!
I can't get used to this stupid greeting.
"I'm the one who recently asked you if
I should confess my love
for my childhood friend."
Oh! It's the person who sent us
a message two episodes ago!
You're amazing... Are you
actually watching this anime?
"All of you cheered me on,
Are you a fan? Are you actually a fan?
but I can't work up the courage because I'm
afraid it might ruin our current friendship."
I totally get that.
"So I was wondering if I could get some
words of encouragement from you again.
Please take care,
and keep up the good work.
Thank you."
There are things you can't say,
however badly you want to.
Totally. "You're being dramatic.
You're laying it on as much as Yae does."
But you might regret it if you don't!
That's one thing I could never say.
Yeah. Since you've known each
other for more than ten years,
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Yeah! You can do it!
So, Chinese Fried Sesame Dumpling-san...
You can do it!
The next message we have is from
Kusure name "Tunamayo-san."
Is that their favorite rice ball filling?
"Nice to meet you. I'm a second-year
in high school, and I love anime.
After I graduate, I'm planning to go
to Tokyo and become a voice actor.
Why did all of you decide
to become voice actors?"
You, Koto-chan?
I've always liked anime,
and before I knew it,
I'd decided I would be one.
Oh, you took that route?
I'm the same. The "I thought
I could just become one" route.
Wait, isn't that different?
I'm not sure that's the same.
No, it's totally the same.
Someone in my family was doing this job,
so I thought that I could do it, too.
So I was influenced by those around me
and my surroundings. You know?
I guess...
See? That does happen.
Was it the same for you, Momoka-chan?
Hmm...
Yeah, well... I guess that was part of it, sort of.
What about you, Kazuha-chan?
I wanted to become an actress,
and I liked acting and anime,
so I decided that was what I wanted to do.
There's no other reason.
R-Right...
No matter how much you like it and want to do it,
if there's no one who understands you,
Don't go too far
and if your surroundings won't allow it...
I'm also not from Tokyo,
just like Tunamayo-san,
so I know how hard that can be.
There are a lot of hurdles
that you have to get over.
So prepare as much as you can right now,
and make your dream come true.
I'll be cheering you on.
Be gentle!
Yeah. There are a lot of difficult things,
but there are a lot of fun things, too!
Yeah, I totally get that.
Right... Well, there's a lot to it.
This turned out to be a really good talk!
Where are we supposed to go after this?
And with that, we've reached the end
of our listener message segment!
So dark!
I am not.
So you're finally on the side of cheering
other people on with their dreams.
I was a bit moved.
I just said what they wanted to hear.
You don't have to be shy.
I'm not!
Anyway, this is my job.
I'm not doing anything weird, right?
Though, I mean, this is just for
promotion and isn't actual acting...
But this is part of my job, too.
And that swimsuit?
Yes. That was also for promotion.
But seeing that was...
That was my first and last time in a swimsuit.
Don't worry about it.
We should probably be a bit
more flexible there...
It was the last time.
Right...
You seem more cheerful
than I thought. I'm relieved.
And you seem to have some wonderful friends.
Can I help you?
You're in front of the exit,
so we couldn't leave.
Yep, yep.
What?
Now, now, now. It can't be helped.
We don't know all the details,
but we can't help being curious.
Kazu-chan, Kazu-chan.
What?
Dad
Incoming Call...
Let your father hear how well you're doing, too.
Wait!
Here? Right now? Is this thing connected?
Dad
Incoming Call...
Well, yes. It is a phone.
Here.
I have nothing to say to him.
Of course you do.
Your father was most worried
after he saw you in that.
I told you about the swimsuit already.
I have nothing more to say.
Hm? Hmm? Foom, foom, foom?
I heard everything, ma'am.
Leave everything to me.
S-Sure...
W-Wait!
Well, hello. This is Kuzu.
Yes, you could say that
I'm in charge of this anime.
Kazuha-chan's been doing great work for us...
Though I'm not the only admiring her great work.
All the young men in the country are, too.
Just kidding!
Really, sir, Kazuha-chan is the
ultimate presence to give
hopes, dreams, and comfort to
young and mature men alike.
Especially the presence of her breasts!
And so, as you can see, we'll take responsibility...
Uh, yes... Right.
I'll hand you over to the one in charge...
Towada! Towada!
Come here!
Yes?
Here.
Huh?
Hello, this is Towada of Peitax...
Yes, Kuzu is my boss... Right.
Seems Papa's a little angry.
Yeah, I'm sure he is. Probably super pissed.
I'm terribly sorry about that.
I am so very sorry!
Kuzu-san, what are you
going to do about this?!
Tee-hee!
If Shibasaki's work is hindered at all,
it'll be a huge loss for our agency!
Now, now. I'll make sure
Towada works things out.
I'm so sorry.
We'll be sure to make it up to you soon,
so please tell your husband...
Please don't worry about that anymore.
I'll talk to my husband.
You should just leave me alone.
Kazu-chan!
Honestly, your body may have grown,
but you're still such a child.
Your father's not always
going to be well, you know.
Huh?
Well, I'll be heading home now.
Are you going to make the shinkansen?
I'll be fine.
I am a proprietress, and leaving all the
work to your father is hard on him.
If you're so busy, you could have just called.
There are a lot of things I can find out
just by seeing your face, too.
Because I'm your mother.
Take care.
Yeah.
She's a great mom.
Shibasaki-san, I think it'd be a good idea
for us to go apologize in person.
Right. We'll make it a day when
you're off, so you should...
No.
But it'd be a bit awkward if it was just us...
So he was angry, then?
I'm not sure if "angry" is the word...
He was just very intense.
There's the thing with Kuzu-san, too,
but we should get him to understand
about the swimsuit and your job.
If he were to show up on site...
But it's pretty far away.
It's half a day away from Tokyo,
and it's in the mountains...
So we'd have to stay at least a night,
or at most, three nights.
Huh?
Wait, you're planning to go with us, Kuzu-san?
I don't have a choice. I'm the boss.
No, we'll handle it...
I know, I know. I totally understand that
you don't want to trouble me.
But it's the producer's job to put out any fires.
Kuzu-san, I'll go, too.
I can't just stand by when
my friend is in need.
Right! That's the obvious thing to feel, right?
Yep! I'm the lead on this show, so I have to go!
Well said! Chi-sama knows exactly
what it means to be at the top.
All right, let's all go.
Yeah! Hot springs, here we come!
I mean, Karasuma Chitose will do her best!
Chi-sama, we see right through you.
Gojo-san's gonna yell at you again.
It's fine. It's for work, anyway!
Chi-chan, we shouldn't do this.
You're not going, Yae? But hot
springs help you lose weight.
Huh?
That's not okay! And I won't lose any weight!
If you'll excuse me.
Right. Great job today.
I'm very sorry. Today was, um...
No, today was a very valuable experience.
Great job, everyone.
Wanna hang out with me for a bit?
Kazuha-sama, here's your drink.
Thanks.
That's the stuff!
Kuzu P and Chi-sama sure
do go above and beyond.
In all the wrong ways.
Work is going to be awkward from tomorrow on.
I hope they don't say anything weird.
I dunno.
Chi-sama doesn't have much interest in others.
The other two aren't the type to say anything,
and neither am I.
True.
So, are you going to go home?
I'm not sure.
I see.
How long has it been since you were home?
About five years.
It might be quite the surprise, then.
True... Since I left home with
the intention of never going back,
I'm sure they'd be quite surprised.
No, no. I mean you're going
to be surprised, Kazuha-sama.
Huh?
Parents tend to get smaller
the longer you don't see them,
and they aren't as young as you think.
Does that mean...
Oh, my parents are just fine.
I see.
But when I go home once in a while,
I'm always surprised at how much they've aged.
No.
Why?! I'm the leader!
The chairman! I have to go to
my friends when they're in need!
Then support them at work.
Not to mention, you're the one
holding everyone back the most.
But Kuzu-san said we should all go...
Since it was an order from the producer,
doesn't that make this work?
No.
Come on! I don't have any work anyway, do I?
I'm just a crappy, small-fry newbie with no work,
so I have all the free time in the world!
How can you say something that
embarrassing so confidently?
I wanna go to the hot springs!
If I don't have good days once in a while,
I'm not going to feel like working.
If you have that much free time,
review your scripts more.
Yamagata's a great place. Let's go once.
Food, transportation, lodging, and gifts...
I'm gonna expense them all!
Gonna eat Yamagata steak,
sukiyaki, and shabu-shabu.
I wanna go! I wanna eat!
Huh?
G-Good morning!
Morning. Are you voicing another character?
Yes!
We seem to be running into you
a lot lately, Kugayama-san.
Y-Yes! They've been letting me
do all kinds of roles lately...
It's a pleasure to work with you again!
That Karasuma from Number One
Produce isn't bad.
Unlike the other Karasuma
from Number One Produce.
Oh, b-but they might be implementing
even more new characters,
so maybe Chi-chan...
I don't know about that.
Also, why are you being so formal with me?
I told you that wasn't necessary.
Oh, well, you are my senpai, Sono-san, so...
You really are completely
different from Chitose.
You can just call me Momoka.
R-Really?
Yes.
Sono Momoka-sama
That makes me feel more at ease.
Kugayama-san, would you
like something to dri—
To be able to call you by your first name...
It's almost like we're friends!
You really do get pitiful at times...
N-No... It's just that in an anime I liked,
they call each other by their last names,
but then there's a scene
where they use first names,
and you feel like they really became friends...
Oh, Pure Para. So you saw that.
Y-You know it?
Well, yeah...
Oh, right! Sono Sakura-san!
I've always liked them...
Pure Para and Sono Sakura-san!
Then you can probably look forward
to the next series, too.
R-Really? Is it that amazing?
What will the toys be like this time?
Er... I just heard a little something.
You know, l-like a rumor.
I can't wait! I wonder which
voice actors are going to be in it.
Pure Para, huh?
Sono Momoka-sama
We'll never give up!
We're going to protect everyone's smiles!
You can do it!
I'll... I'll do my best, too!
Don't lose!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You can do it!
I'll... I'll do my best, too!
Don't lose!
You don't have to worry about it.
Oh, nah, I was gonna head to bed anyway.
I see.
U-Um, hey...
That swimsuit thing was pretty well-received,
and I got some offers
to do some gravure stuff...
I see. I can't say I'm very fond of that.
So you're against it?
Of course not.
If it's something you want
to try, I won't stop you.
You're popular for your pure and cute image,
so I just thought it'd be better if
you didn't stray too far from that.
It probably won't go over very well
with the Pure Para audience, either.
Oh, you're right. I guess my
image is important, too.
But in the end, it's your decision to make.
You're already a professional, Momoka.
Right. Thanks.
Well, goodnight.
So stupid.
Hey,
You might have already heard from your mom, but the dinner meeting for
Pure Para's been scheduled, so I'm contacting you. I'll send you the details
in another message, so make sure you look at it. They seem pretty excited
about this and might have invited too many people. Well, see you later.
I didn't hear anything about that.
Tokyo Station at 7:00 AM!!
If you're late, you're gonna buy me a drink!!
I'm so excited!!
Hot springs! Table tennis! Pillow fights!
Inn food that you can eat for free is so good!!
She's so stupid.
Idiot
Thanks
Night~
So am I, though...
Shut up...
I don't have work.
I don't have work forever.
The Yamagata-bound
shinkansen Tsubasa 128 leaving at 7:28
Morning! Look, I bought some Jet shumai!
will be arriving shortly.
Tsubasa
Yamagata | Shinjo
I booked us some seats.
Thank you.
Good morning.
What?!
What's that dumb look for? Let's go.
Preview
Why are you here?
Well, Yamagata's famous for its hot springs!
It's great for your skin and detoxing.
No way it's really that effective.
Let's see what a body that grew up
in a hot springs inn looks like!
Oh? It's actually pretty voluptuous.
Oh, come on. Stop that!
Take that, you!
Does anyone actually have
trash conversations like this?
I've never seen one.
Good. That means you'll get to
experience it for the first time.
What are you talking about?
Well, we'll be going in the hot springs
together, right? Not that I know.
What?