Kanazawa
Shinjo
Niigata
Kanazawa
Jet shumai are so good!
Sorry! I can't go today!
I suddenly got, like,
work, or something?
Actually, I don't have work, but...
No, really, I was totally planning on going.
But like, Gojo-kun broke
his promise, or something?
Yeah, it's totally unforgivable!
It's all Gojo-kun's fault! I'm so pissed!
Hiss!
This is a super popular local souvenir.
I recommend this. I totally recommend this.
She really is a character...
More importantly...
What?
You didn't really have to come, either.
Well, we're friends, aren't we?
We don't have time for that.
Yeah, well...
Kawahara Mutsumi
Incoming Call...
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm doing this for myself.
We're here! Haisai, Yamagata!
You're going to piss off people
from both Yamagata and Okinawa.
It's still two hours from
here on trains and buses.
Haisai?!
Manju
#08 Oversleeping Chitose and a Steamy Travel Mood
Oh, this is so Japan!
Geisha, onsen, harakiri!
I wonder if he'd really consider
slicing his stomach open...
His neck, too.
Kazu-chan! We've been waiting
for you. Welcome home.
Yeah...
Thank you all for coming this far.
Please, come in.
I'm sorry.
I told him that all of you were coming...
No, no. Please, don't worry about us.
These sweets are delicious, ma'am!
I'm so glad I came! Haisai, Yamagata!
Kuzu-san!
Oh, is he home how?
Welcome home. Kazu-chan
and her guests are here.
Honored Papa!
Huh?
I'm truly sorry for what happened.
Thank you for looking after my daughter.
Huh?
How nice of them to come
all the way out here. Right?
You even brought our daughter.
We're truly grateful.
U-Um... Our agency truly looks forward
to seeing Kazuha-san's continued hard work.
Do you think she'll last?
It's definitely a business of chance,
so I can't make any guarantees...
But I think she's very talented.
Did you hear that?
Isn't that wonderful, darling?
She's a rather imperfect and foolish girl,
but please, continue to guide her.
Your dad doesn't seem opposed.
That's just a front. I'm going to go end this.
Hello.
Can't you even say hello properly?
What do you mean? You're no better.
Kazu-chan!
Well...
Come, now, don't leave your friend waiting.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Sono Momoka.
I work together with
Shibasaki-san on this anime.
Why did you bring that?
Please, take these, if you'd like...
Stop it!
Your mother seemed relieved
after she saw you at work,
so I thought it'd be nice for your father
to see what you were in, at least.
There were better ones you could have picked.
Sorry about that...
Oh, no... I'm not blaming you, Towada-san.
It's more...
I heard someone call my name.
Huh? What?
You don't have to watch those.
Kazuha.
If you're truly an actress,
don't belittle a project you appeared in.
How do I hate you so,
when I am so happy to see you,
just like the first blossom
of the autumn bush clover?
I've acted on those projects,
so I know what they're worth.
They're all the same. They're just
mass-produced generic shows.
What I want to work on isn't
something so worthless. It's more...
Then what does that make you,
if you're in something so worthless?
That's right.
I'm just a worthless voice
actress who's perfect for
showing up in all these
worthless template anime.
That's why I have to resort to something
so mindless as wearing a swimsuit to sell them.
I'm sorry for being such an
imperfect, foolish daughter!
Are you happy now?
Kazu-chan!
You should go back there.
Go back? You're the one who
told me to come home!
Go back to Tokyo. You're one of
them Tokyo folk now, aren't you?
You wanted to be an actress so bad
that you left Yamagata behind.
Stop your yammering and go do
what you can, you foolish daughter.
I don't need you to tell me to go back.
I hate this place!
Kazu-chan!
Are you done? Did you win?
Are you already going back?
Was this a day trip?
What about the hot springs?
What about table tennis...
Shibasaki, wait a minute.
Let go of me!
I don't want to spend another second here.
I think you've got the wrong idea.
What?
Kazuha, I'm going to prepare rooms
for all of you, so stay the night.
Just leave her be and let her go on back.
Oh, hush yer mouth!
If they're paying, they're customers!
Or what? Do you have a problem with that, too?
No.
Where are you from, ma'am?
Then we'll take you up on that, just for tonight.
What are you thinking?
I don't really want to say the
same thing as Kuzu-san, but...
I haven't even gone sightseeing yet.
Look what they gave me.
I always think this at our handout events,
but you're really good at talking
to people you don't know.
Snow Soft Serve
How many years do you think
I've been in this business?
You should talk casually to people more.
I hate it...
O-Oh?
Dealing with people in the country.
They're always giving and exchanging things.
Oh, that.
I thought you were dissing
our handout events.
Seriously...
Though I don't like those at all, either.
Blunt, aren't you?
Always smiling awkwardly
and just doing your best
to keep up appearances...
That kind of thing is like...
Is like?
I and everyone in this town
are all the same...
It's stupid.
It's a small town, isn't it?
It's such a small country town, we could
probably circle it all while talking.
Though I'm sure you probably
wouldn't understand that.
Yeah, I don't understand at all.
Are you mocking me?
Kawahara Mutsumi
Incoming Call...
You're not answering?
I don't feel like it.
I see.
I don't recommend climbing those.
There's only a shrine at the top.
There's nothing else.
Hey, Shibasaki.
What?
I really don't understand
anything that you say.
Because I'm envious of you.
Huh?
Hey...
What's with you?
Don't say I didn't warn you!
I'm gonna head back!
I love hot springs!
By the way, I was really surprised.
Don't push me!
About what?
Don't you dare push me! Don't do it!
Sono-san. Asking her to come along
for support was a great idea.
Hot!
Huh? Wasn't it Iroha Pro
that asked her to come?
Of course not.
There's no way we could have
asked her when she's so busy.
That goes for us, too...
Wait... Isn't this bad?
Hey, Towada, are you listening to me?
I should've brought Mai Mai-chan, too.
Yeah, sure.
Who's Mai Mai-chan?
A hostess he's fond of.
Ah...
This is great! Now if I only had a hot girl,
I'd be in paradise... heaven...
and this world would be bliss.
Despite how he looks now,
he really was amazing at his previous job.
Why don't we have some drinks tonight?
Yeah.
Come here, meow.
It must be great being you.
You don't have to keep meowing to be cute.
Right, meow?
How do you stay so purrfectly cute?
I really don't know what to do, meow.
I-I'm going to die. What's with those stairs?
I told you I didn't recommend them.
But you didn't have to beat me here.
Were you just talking to someone?
Who knows? You were probably
just hearing things.
Oh, really?
I really don't know what to do, meow.
You heard me?
You really are childish in the weirdest
ways, like talking to a cat.
You're not going back to the inn?
You don't want to go back, do you?
Well, I don't need you to keep me company.
I'm the same way.
Katakura-san
Do you happen to know where Momoka-chan is?
She has something important to be at,
and they can't get a hold of her...
Gojo-san said that
her manager was super worried.
She wanted to know if
any of us had any information.
Phone call?
No... I mean, yes.
From Karasuma-san.
Is she asking about her souvenir?
Something like that.
Hey.
The view is much nicer over here.
This is nice.
Is it?
I honestly prefer Tokyo.
Because that's the only place I have.
But this is a nice town,
with nice people, and nice parents.
Parents?
Your dad.
Where are you even looking?
He's naggy, and he pushes his
own values onto other people.
What's so good about that?
The part where he's naggy and pushes
his own values onto other people, I think.
My parents used to be decent.
They would take me to dubbing sessions a lot.
You're rather fortunate.
Then, one time, I was in an anime,
though just as part of the crowd dialogue.
My mom showed me how to use my voice,
and my dad was the series
director for that project.
My debut role that no one knows about.
But once I debuted,
they stopped telling me anything anymore.
I have no clue what you're talking about.
I'm almost envious.
Right. That's what I thought about you earlier.
One sec.
Sure.
Mom
Call
Work
Hello, Kawahara-san?
It's me, Momoka.
I'm very sorry for making you worry.
I'm at a friend's place right now.
Huh? My mom's there?
Mom?
Yeah, I'm not going to the dinner.
No, it's not that.
I'm not going to be in Pure Para.
Pure Para?
Yeah.
If they personally offer me
a role, I'll consider it.
You're talking like a beginner.
But I guess you have a point.
You're only seventeen.
I'd forgotten about that.
You could at least remember
how old your own kid is.
Age doesn't matter with professionals.
You're right. I guess we're both professionals.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
No, it's something that you,
as the actress, decided.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Then I'll just have to tell them
that I'll play the heroine.
Huh?
I guess our second project
together will have to wait.
I'll be waiting, my rival.
Right.
I'll catch up to you soon.
Wait for me, Senpai.
You declined Pure Para?
Oh, well, yeah...
What a waste. It's a Sunday morning show!
My mom said she'd do it instead.
Huh?
It's sort of amazing that my mom
will be playing a middle-schooler.
Let's head back.
Sure.
Bring me more sake!
Seriously, my boss is so hopeless!
Yeah, there are worthless bosses like that!
Guys who never try fail at everything they do.
Seriously. Isn't there anything
we can do about him?
No way!
Yeah, I totally feel you.
Once they dry up, there's no coming back.
It's hopeless!
Just get rid of him!
You need to just take over!
Yeah! You're the only one
who can do it, Towadacchi!
I guess I have no choice, then...
Yeah! Make him lose his position at work!
Okay, here's to Towadacchi
moving up in the world!
Cheers!
Awful...
You need to watch how much you drink, too.
I don't get drunk like that.
What?
Momoka-chan! How did you like this town?
It was a lot of fun!
That's good to hear.
You seemed a bit down, so...
How could you tell?
Well, I am a mother. I can tell just by looking.
What does that mean?
I mean, even with the swimsuits...
Your father was saying how
your smile seemed odd.
Odd?
You love being a voice actress, don't you?
So he was just saying it must be hard on you
if they were forcing you to do things like that.
Well, that's...
It's your job. Of course it's not always fun.
There'll be many tough times and
things you don't want to do,
but that's your job.
Your father's pretty knowledgeable
about voice actors.
When you said that you were
going to become a voice actor,
he did so much research.
Why? He didn't say anything about that...
He has a hard time saying
how he feels... Just like you.
Because you're both from this town.
Your parents will always be your parents.
It's our job to say things to motivate you,
and it's also our job to believe in you and wait.
See? You're loved.
You, too.
I have an easier time
understanding your family.
The grump at my house
just looks mad all the time.
What?
Well, you're also a grump!
I guess the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Shut up!
Now you've done it!
Take that!
Jeez!
What do you think you're doing, you dunce?
I am not a dunce!
Goodness, you can hear them loud and clear.
Her voice always did carry well.
If it's too hard on you,
why don't you stay here forever?
Isn't that a bit cold?
Isn't that really cold? So cold!
Kazu-chan.
I'm heading out.
Make sure you don't catch a cold.
You too, Dad!
Tokyo
I forgot about Karasuma-san's souvenir.
"Chitose" is good enough
for someone like her.
Someone like her?
People like her,
and people like you...
This business is filled with them.
You're right.
It's filled with people like you.
I wonder what I should do
for Chitose's souvenir.
I don't really think she needs one.
You've got a point.
Hot springs, shabu-shabu...
Read by 4
Yeah, it's totally unforgivable!
It's all Gojo-kun's fault!  I'm so pissed!
Hiss
Reading and ignoring my
messages from Yamagata...
Is it because of the time difference?
A time difference, huh...
Well, Yamagata is pretty far.
Preview
Do you even know what
a time difference is?
Of course I do.
The reason I couldn't get up this
morning was because of jet lag.
No, you're just an idiot.
You didn't go to Yamagata,
so you need to practice more.
Practice? Despite how I look,
I practice quite a bit.
And I'm telling you it's not enough.
At this rate, you're going to lose your job.
What the heck? That's hilarious.
I haven't said a single hilarious thing.
Oh, come on. That's not happening.
I'm the main heroine.
I wonder if that's actually the case...
Wait, I'm not?