И первый приз уходит...
Выступавшей под номером 3!
Сакурагаоке Нанами-сан!
Спасибо вам большое!
Я буду стараться изо всех сил, чтобы стать ещё лучше.
Спасибо вам всем!
Она невероятна.
Нам треба работать швидче, тэж.
Да… Нам, как её наставникам,
предстоит многому её обучить.
А разве мы можем её чему-то научить?
Конечно, есть!
У нас второй сезон «Кусурэ» на носу.
On the contrary, it wouldn't
be an exaggeration to say that
we're at the top of the voice acting business.
On the contrary or not,
that's definitely an exaggeration.
I was just trying to say that
Яэ should be more confident.
Because we're the senpai voice actors!
#09「Обеспокоенная Титосэ и Неудержимый Новобранец」
It's so cold!
Showing up just barely on time
right when the cour starts?
How many times did you
plan to go back to sleep?
It's fine, Годзё-кун. You know what they say...
"A well-slept child is a well-kept child."
You should just look at the big picture
and see that I'm maturing gradually.
Just who do you think you are,
to be talking like that?
Good morning.
Mokochaka
Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
Good morning.
It's a pleasure to work with you again today.
I'm sorry. That trash p—
I mean, our producer, Кудзу,
is running late today.
Worst case, he might not show up at all.
I'm very sorry.
Did he just call him something diff—
That's fine, but will it push back the start time?
No, that won't be an issue.
You can just consider Кудзу to be dead,
and go ahead and start without him.
Right...
Well, I look forward to
working with you today.
It's the first episode and that trash—
Кудзу-сан isn't coming?
Well, it's the second cour.
Right. It's the second cour
of a title that didn't sell.
Stop putting words in my mouth.
Save reading between the
lines for when you're acting.
Okay.
The audience ran away,
and now the producer ran away.
Yet we just can't escape from being in the red.
Pardon me... Do you have a moment?
Yes, thank you.
It's rare for you to actually ask
about the source material.
Of course I would. This is my job.
You mean our job.
Ahem...
Hello, there. We've come to observe today.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
Hey, boss!
How about a round?
Nah, I can't. I'm still working.
But boss, Май Май-тян,
who loves anime, is lonely.
But they just can't seem to
do anything if I'm not there.
Товада? Man, this is killing me!
I'm three hours late. I'll be there in a bit...
Huh? It's done? You Пареньs are out drinking now?
Well, I mean, if I'm not there, the party won't...
No one mentioned anything?
Oh, okay... I'll go if I have time.
Did you say Май Май-тян was here today?
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming today,
despite your busy schedules.
In any event, it'll be a pleasure to work
with all of you again starting this week.
Cheers!
Hello, hello.
Thanks for having us today.
Thank you very much! I learned a lot today.
Oh, no! Let me.
No, no, no...
You shouldn't...
I do this for my father, too.
How nostalgic.
I remember being new like that.
You had a huge attitude to begin with.
Found me out, huh?
Thanks.
Oh, no. I'm the newbie,
so this should be expected.
You don't have to be so formal.
But it's cool havin' someone younger
than me in the agency for once.
Кото-тян, haven't you always been the oldest?
Hm?
Oh, nothing...
A kohai, huh... It kinda feels nice.
Yeah, now I feel like I have
to work even harder, too.
Нанами-тян, if you need anything, let me know.
Yes, I'll do my absolute best.
It's a pleasure to be in your care, Senpai.
"Senpai"... It has such a nice ring to it.
I'm not sure if we're worthy of that title.
I mean, our first Майn
roles were for this show.
W-Well, we still have a ways to go.
Today might be the first time you've heard us act,
but that'll be a super rare experience later on...
Oh, it's not the first time!
Um... I watched all of the Kusure anime.
Karasuma-сан, that scream you did
as Yuna in episode 5 was so good.
Huh? Really? You saw it?
Yes. I've read the original work,
so I was really moved to see
my favorite characters
with voices and movement.
Oh-ho! So you were impressed with the
super acting skills of the superdimensional
Cinderella Девушка, Karasuma Титосэ-тян,
who also sold 10,000 CDs?
Yes! I decided to audition because
I was inspired by you, Karasuma-senpai!
I feel so blessed to be able to meet you!
I see! It'll be nice if we can
work together someday.
I mean, if we have two Cinderellas
together, we've basically won.
You're amazing, Karasuma-сан!
Now, come on, Chi-сама, you shouldn't...
You're harmonizing so well,
yet totally out of tune.
Титосэ, seriously...
Stop spewing that baloney!
It's 'cause you say them things
that you're stuck in the same spot!
B-Balo...?
Balo... Baloney?
Damn, Кадзуха-сама, yer lettin'
yer accent come out again.
Кото-тян, yours is coming out, too!
The way you usually talk
just slips out sometimes.
I actually end up calling
Годзё-кун "Манаger" sometimes.
That's actually true...
That doesn't matter.
Where's your family from again?
Ibaraki? Yamagata?
I still haven't gotten a souvenir from that trip.
Souvenirs don't matter!
You're the problem!
There's someone who's debuted after you now.
You can't call yourself a newbie anymore.
You've now become a legitimate professional.
You need to really think about that.
I see...
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yeah, Shibasaki-сан...
Oh, I guess I should call you "Кадзуха-тян" now.
I'm kinda moved that you would
say that about me, Кадзуха-тян.
Wh-What are you...
So you're finally seeing me for who I really am.
S-Seriously, you don't get it at all!
Yeah, Титосэ. You should actually listen to her.
Baloney there is trying to think about
your future in her own special way.
Stop saying "baloney."
Oh, come on, Baloney.
Have some more to drink, Baloney.
That's a woman from the north for you.
A legitimate pro, huh...
I mean, I'm a legitimate pro,
so I gave the committee a piece of my mind.
I bet you did!
I mean, entertainment isn't about numbers.
I had no idea.
Yeah, only people who are actually working
on the project understand these things...
That's amazing!
Nah... I mean, it's only natural for me,
since I see everything as entertainment.
Since you're here, why don't
we have another bottle?
Hm? Oh, sure.
That's why I love you, Кудзу-сан!
Oh, really? Well, I am pretty loaded.
Really? That's an anime producer for you!
You love anime, don't you, Май Май-тян?
Maybe I'll bring a voice actor with me next time.
Really?
What anime do you like, by the way?
Let's see...
Out of the ones I've seen recently,
there's this,
and this...
I see, I see...
Титосэ! What do you think about it?
Good question...
You changin' the subject?
Shibasaki-сан, let's drink something else.
U-Um...
I heard you talking... Is it
true that you liked Kusure?
Yes! I have the first press for each volume.
I'm collecting all the store bonuses, too.
I see. I'm sure Sensei will be happy to hear that.
What did you think of the anime?
It was great!
Oh, come on. There must be something
more you'd like to say about it.
No!
I really, really love Kusure,
so I really enjoyed watching every episode.
I-I see...
But if there was one thing...
One thing?
I wish a lot more people had watched it.
Kusure is so good.
I hope that
more people are able to see that.
Yeah...
I'm truly blessed today for being
able to see behind the scenes
and meet so many people
involved with Kusure.
I...
will continue to work even harder!
We need to put in the work
to make a great series
and regain the viewers that we lost.
I think it'd be better to create a buzz
with something new and
reach an unknown crowd.
The anime and original story sides
need to work together...
Um... I'll participate in even more events.
Not just the handout events,
but something else...
Yeah, but the agency has
their own responsibilities,
so we can't really make
that decision on our own.
Oh, right...
But we would all like to do whatever we can.
Right, Кадзуха–sama?
Heck yeah!
Are you Пареньs talking about
something fun? Let me join.
Where did she...
I-I-I ate way too much... Годзё-кун!
We're going to change
how we do the radio show?
Yes. We've been doing it
after the dubbing sessions,
but there were a lot of limitations.
So now we're going to work
with various shops to record it.
But will all of our schedules line up?
Well, we'll probably have to make
some adjustments here and there...
We'll just have to work it out step by step.
Uh, and where will we be going?
That's being worked out.
We thought it'd be good
to throw out some ideas.
I see...
Is this another one of Кудзу-сан's ideas?
Ah... No...
But we've gotten permission,
so everything is fine.
Okay...
Official Channel
Broadcasting Live
User
Broadcast
Broadcast Live
By Popularity
Millennium Princess x Kowloon
Overlord KusuRadio
Official Channel
Broadcasting Live
User
Broadcast
Broadcast Live
By Popularity
Millennium Princess x Kowloon
Overlord KusuRadio
All right, we're going to start the test.
We're ready.
Is the trash... I mean, Кудзу-сан here yet?
Ah, no, he's running behind with other work,
so he said he'll come if he can.
I mean, if we can just go through you,
Товада-сан, that works, too.
No, I don't think that's good.
I just hope Кудзу-сан feels more
motivated to show up here...
Yeah, that's not happening.
He wasn't always trash.
He was famous for working really hard
before he came to our agency.
So I keep believing that he'll
help us out in the end...
It was great back in the day!
If we released DVDs, they sold.
So you were really amazing!
But streaming is being
killed by illegal uploads,
so the business scheme has changed.
I see.
So anyway, it's almost my birthday!
Where's Май Май-тян?
Oh, sorry.
Looks like someone else picked her today.
Oh, come on, Сякудзии-сан.
You're going to drink more, aren't you?
I love when you're like that.
Do you know each other?
He's a former coworker who
started at the same time I did.
Кудзу quit the company
and got a different job,
but I'm still with the company.
And you can see the difference between us.
I could hear your voice
from all the way over there.
You never change.
You still haven't grown up.
Could I get my check, please?
Where are you going?
I'm going to drink somewhere else.
You're running away again?
Huh?
Just like you lost to me
at work and ran away...
Are you running away again here?
What did you say?
You used to have more of a backbone.
Hey, Сякудзии-сан, let's hurry
back so we can drink more.
Should we have Dom? Or Peri?
Wait just a moment, okay?
Oh, please! I'll wait as long as you want!
You're always like that...
You steal everything from me...
promotions, women,
and now the oasis for my soul.
What are you going to do about it?
I'm going to win this time!
And then I'm going to get
my Май Май-тян back!
I don't belong to you, Кудзу-сан.
I know that!
Damn it! Damn it!
Ow...
Hey.
Damn it...
Hello, Кудзу-сан? Where are you?
Товада, save me!
The second installment of
that major hit anime!
The role of a lifetime has arrived.
I've already won!
I have no idea what makes you
think you'll pass that audition.
Not to mention, there's a limit of
one person per role per agency.
Which means?
We have to limit how many people audition.
I see. That sucks for everyone else.
What makes you think
you're going to be the one?
It's almost my birthday,
so that'd be the perfect present.
Are you the center of the world?
Oh, about that...
Talent Profile
Name: Сакурагаока Нанами
Reading: Сакурагаока Нанами
Birthday: 4/7
Birthplace: Tokyo
Dialect: None
Hobbies: Living a well-balanced life
Skills: Softball
Full Name (Birth Name): Сакурагаока Нанами
Birthday: 4/7
Надпись: Aries
Blood Type: O
Age 18 (Actual age can be disclosed)
Birthplace: Tokyo
Address: Chofu City, Tokyo
Family: Lives at home with her mother and father. An only child.
We want her to audition.
Huh?
Sir, that's not what we discussed...
This matter is...
I'm sorry!
But after seeing her at the party the
other day, I felt she could do it.
The party? Do what?
I mean, Титосэ-кун
started out the same way.
Don't we want her to take
flight like Титосэ-кун has?
Huh? U-Um, I...
Well, with Титосэ-кун,
I think it's about time she takes
the next step and tries for \Нанамиrration and foreign film dubs.
H-Huh?!
Yep, yep, yep.
No, no, no, no...
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
No, no, no, no, no!
Yep, yep, yep!
No, no, yep...?
Yep, yep, yep?
No way...
Sir, that's not possible.
Титосэ isn't even secure with anime as it is...
Годзё-кун... You're exactly right.
And that's exactly why!
Титосэ-кун and Нанами-тян
will both be our poster girls!
What I'm saying is...
Just try to remember, Годзё-кун...
When you were a voice actor,
you got a lead role around this time.
The youth have every right to dream,
and it's our duty to sell them that dream.
And so, Годзё-кун, you'll be in charge
of the new girl from now on.
I expect the best from you,
our most capable Манаger!
Huh? Годзё-кун is going to be
both my Манаger and Нанами's?
Oh, no. We'll get you a different
tactful Манаger, Титосэ-кун.
You'll have your own Манаger!
A different... But that's...
Yep, yep!
Number One Produce will keep
moving toward the future
on even more solid footing!
Good morning.
Oh... Yeah.
Sorry, I got called away suddenly,
so let's talk another time.
I'm home.
You're home late. Did you
have a lot to talk about?
It was late, so I made
sure she got home safe.
She's still in high school.
Huh...
More importantly, why are you
dressed like that? You'll catch a cold.
That's sexual harassment!
A Манаger is sexually harassing an idol!
This is a huge scandal that'll
Сякудзииe the whole industry!
This means he'll have to lose all of his
current charges, doesn't it,
Commentator Karasuma-сан?
It's not going to Сякудзииe the industry,
and you're not an idol to begin with.
I should be a worthy commodity
to market as an idol.
Do you not understand my worth, Годзё-кун?
You don't have any worth.
I wonder if the agency has
any plans to market me.
I think they need to reconsider my Манаger.
You really are trash for switching
the blame onto the agency.
You're not even in charge
of me anymore, Годзё-кун!
You sold your soul to the evil agency!
Quit making stupid false accusations.
Stupid? It's not stupid...
You've got it easy, Годзё-кун.
You have a job where you don't have to do
anything and still get paid every month.
That was my decision.
The same goes for you. You chose this.
Yeah, but...
I didn't! I didn't!
At this rate, I might end up
quitting as a voice actor
after just having one lead role,
just like you, Годзё-кун.
You're not answering that?
Yes.
Hello! Um,
thank you so much for everything today.
Preview
Годзё-сан, I'll try to work even harder.
I'll put effort first, second, third,
fourth, all the way to a hundred!
If I don't work hard,
it'll be rude to Karasuma-сан.
Huh? Oh, you think so?
Karasuma-сан's really amazing!
Well, I also think that if she'd just—
She's cute, confident,
and completely transparent!
Oh, right...
I want to be like Karasuma-сан!
Please, no. One Karasuma
Титосэ is more than enough.