Добрый день!
Я — Мацуока, твой менеджер!
Прошу, зови меня Маццу!
Ха-ха!
Э… Мацу…ока…
Отныне ты будешь моим помощником.
Ты не уходишь?!
Я сказал президенту, что не могу
так быстро сдать свои полномочия.
Вот оно что. Получается, я — младший менеджер.
О… Выходит, всё таки, ты остаёшься.
Понимаю! Чувства Карасумы-сан
больно ранят меня!
А? Что?
Да кто я такой, в сравнении с ветераном Годзё-саном!
Но! Но знаешь что…
Это напряжение даёт шанс
созреть, как специалисту!
«Тугая пружина сильнее распрямляется!»
А? Ух…
Я серьёзно настроен поддерживать тебя!
Поэтому, Карасума-сан,
ударьте меня со всей силы!
Буду рад!
Очень рада знакомству…
#10 「Титосэ Погружается во Тьму и Разочарованный Кудзу」
Берём перерыв.
Отлично потрудились.
Японский Словарь Вокала и Актёрского Мастерства
Я умственно переутомляюсь от этих ролей за массвоку.
Думать, чтобы кто-то, вроде меня,
кто играет главные роли,
был столь осторожным…
Разве это не делает меня
мастером тактичности?
Эм…
Карасума-сан, отличная работа!
Оу, спасибо… Стой, а что ты тут делаешь?
I'll be recording here after this,
so I came early to observe everyone.
Huh… I'm always responsible myself,
but you're pretty responsible, too, Нанами.
You should relax more
when you're voice acting.
D-Definitely not!
Unlike you, Карасума-сан, I'm still…
still very much a newbie!
Oh, we're not that different.
Plus, I'm starting college next year.
College students are proper
adults with responsibilities.
O-Oh…
I have my mom and dad and
other people cheering me on,
so I have to push forward
with everything I have.
W-Well, yeah… It's important
to always feel like that.
I'm actually going to be a year
older this month, myself…
Oh, really?! Congratulations!
We'll have to celebrate!
Nah, you don't have to.
You're so sweet, Нанами. You make
me want to take care of you.
Great job. Your next appointment is at 4:00 PM.
We'd have to walk from the station to the
next studio, so why don't we get a taxi?
Nice joke!
After observing you working
these past few days,
I see that you definitely
have a lot of potential.
Huh? Really? You really think so?
Yes, I'm certain! You should be
able to get even more popular!
I knew it! You're the type of person
who understands my worth, aren't you?
But reality doesn't always work that way.
What do you think you lack, Карасума-сан?
Enthusiasm from my agency
in promoting me.
Nice joke!
Yes, it's hard work!
Huh?
Hard work first, and hard work second.
Hard work third, and hard work until you die!
You need a certain period of your career
where you're at the bottom of the pole!
Hard Work and Being at the Bottom
The bottom?
First, you need sensibility.
Please read all of these.
So many…
Yes!
There are many, many fun things in this world!
That is the happiest thing for anyone
involved in entertainment!
So, I realize this is sudden,
but I went ahead and booked some
mob roles for you, starting next week.
Huh?
The sound director for this job
likes acting that's natural,
so I think you'll learn a lot.
Let's do our best!
Wait, wait. Next week is such short notice…
The ball always comes at you suddenly!
You must hit that chance ball, no matter what!
Otherwise, you can't win the match!
R-Right… Match?
Карасума Титосэ-сан!
There are those who do one mob role after
another, then get promoted to a lead role!
Everyone wants to go after that ball!
The recording booth is the center court!
The voice actor is the player!
You understand, right?
Huh? No…
There are many other people in
your position, Карасума-сан!
You want one of them to take the ball?!
Of course not! You can't let
them have it, can you?!
R-Right…
I can't hear you!
Элитное Жильё здесь
Дайканъяма
Louder!
Right!
Yes! Let's do our best! I'll work
as if my life depended on it, too!
Let's die doing our best together!
R-Right…
I can't hear you! Louder!
Right!
Nice and loud! Well done!
There is currently a problem
with the rail Надписьal,
so all lines will be postponing operations.
Glamourous Housing is Here
Daikanyama
We apologize for the inconvenience.
This isn't good! We won't make it in time!
Then let's get a taxi….
Let's run!
Hard work first, hard work second,
and hard work even if it kills you!
No… This isn't the time to be looking back.
Yes… Yes. Yes, please do.
This is great!
I'm starting to see a Cinderella story.
What might you mean by that?
Нанами-кун. Нанами Sakuragaoka.
She didn't get the lead, but they
wanted her for a different role.
That's great. That'll be a
motivator for everyone else, too.
That girl might just take the whole country!
She's cute, too, so I think she'll become popular.
We've won!
Sir… The new girl is great,
but we need to keep an eye
on those who are having trouble growing…
Such as?
Such as…
Someone who had one lead role,
but hasn't landed another since.
Katakura-кун and Яэ-тян are both doing fine.
They're both getting roles,
and getting more work.
Um, there's one more…
Ah, Титосэ Карасума?
Right.
Hm… Then conversely… Conversely,
why don't we prep Нанами-кун for a lead role?
Huh?
For our next agency event,
why don't we plan a big surprise?
No, wait…
And conversely, Титосэ-кун
may have a chance of leveling up.
No, she won't.
Why's that?
You said so many times yourself, Годзё-кун.
She never takes things seriously.
There are plenty who could take her place.
Well, yes…
I feel like I've waited quite long enough
for Титосэ-кун,
and for you, too, Годзё-кун.
That's…
A manager is neither a parent nor a teacher.
This is strictly business.
If someone shows no promise,
I have to cut them.
Does she have promise?
More than me, at least…
I'm sorry. Please just give me a little more time.
Oh? I didn't order this.
On the house for a nice person
Whew! Aren't I quite the actor?
An old man who can act!
Maybe I'll start a senior class
at the training school.
I'm saying…
Take a closer look!
It's about forty centimeters long!
Er… But it's actually two
centimeters short of forty…
My Mai Mai-тян tends to shrink and grow.
Please don't randomly name it…
Cut me a little slack!
Anyone Who Catches a Fish Measuring
40cm or More Will Get This Sticker
No one's gonna want these stickers!
Then you don't need it, do you?
Come on… I'll never be able
to beat him at this rate.
That doesn't concern me…
We're closing now.
Catch another big one some other time.
Товада!
I asked you to save me,
and you didn't call me back once!
Damn it… Damn it!
I don't have anyone, anyway.
My future is pitch black…
Ти-сама, what's wrong?
You seem really tired today.
Hmm… I'd say it's more lately, not just today.
You okay?
This is our agency's event,
and we're counting on you as the lead.
Yeah, I know…
Карасума-сан!
Let's rehearse the Песня once more!
You can do it much, much
better, Карасума-сан!
Uh, but it's just rehearsal…
Why don't you do your best?!
Do you think you can do in a match
what you can't do in practice?!
You can't, right?!
Right…
I can't hear you! Louder!
Right!
Nice and loud! Well done!
You can see what my sub-manager is like.
I wonder if he thinks I'm a newbie or something…
P-Pardon me. Could I get the
playback on my ear monitor
a bit louder, please?
Is your playback okay, Нана-тян?
Yes! This is the first time
I've worn an ear monitor!
So I don't really understand it, but I'll be fine!
You don't understand it, but it's fine?
Yes! I'll do my best either way!
I don't want to move another inch.
Are we going to be okay tomorrow?
It's always nerve-wracking before an event.
Really? This isn't our first
time doing this. We'll be fine.
That's our Карасума-сан for you!
I'll do my best, too!
The audience capacity this time is a thousand…
Even if we pull a big crowd,
it's the merch sales…
Does that have anything to do with us?
If we're thinking about whether our
customers will be satisfied or not,
it means as much to us
as ants do to an anteater.
What's with the awful pun?
N-No, it's a joke from a light novel anime that's
about to start where I'm one of the leads.
Huh… So you've downgraded
from anime professor
to light novel professor.
Well, anyway,
we're not brand-spanking-new newbies anymore.
Right. So we have to straighten up.
We have to act more like professionals.
That means, since I am a newbie,
I need to try much, much, much harder!
Годзё-сан! Please let me practice one more time!
Well, I guess one more wouldn't hurt…
Thank you very much!
Then I'll give it another go, too!
M-Me, too!
How long do you plan on lying there?
Where'd that come from, Годзё-кун?
There's no one around you.
You're the only one stuck in place.
Are you just going to let
yourself get left behind?
You're exaggerating. Okay, I'll go, I'll go.
I'm heading out.
I'll be waiting.
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
I can do this. I can do this.
It'll be okay! It'll be okay!
I can do this! I can do this!
I'm getting nervous! I'll do my best!
I'll do my best and get nervous!
You guys are thinkin' about it too much.
B-But…
Then let's talk about something
that'll calm your nerves.
Y'know, about the celebration for Ти-сама…
Oh, the surprise present?
Were you going to give
the first Надписьal, Кото-тян?
They haven't figured out the surprise yet?
The president said to go out with
a bang since it's a special occasion.
Well, we have to figure out the staging…
Is Katakura-сан supposed to cue the lighting?
Make sure you tell her.
A surprise? Oh, for my birthday…
Take the picture and up it!
The mysterious luminescence is the star!
Tons of filters! Science is a girl's best friend…
This is sudden, but we actually
have a surprise for you now!
Wow! That's amazing!
H-Huh? I wonder what it could be…
It's…
Нанами-тян's CD debut!
Congratulations!
The words I can say in my dreams are so
embarrassing once I'm out of my dream
I know I probably can't say them to your face
Going with the rhythm, 1, 2, 3!
I just started humming to play it off
I can't sing, but that's part of my charm!
Please, just wake me up already!
Morning, I rub my tired eyes
as the morning sun shines in
Happy birthday, Ти-сама!
Happy birthday, Ти-тян!
Happy birthday!
Wasn't that a perfect surprise?
Were you surprised?
Huh? U-Um…
Ти-тян?
No… I'm sorry.
It's just that I was genuinely surprised…
Aw, Ти-сама, you can
actually be cute sometimes.
Hurry up and blow out the candles!
It's so good.
It is!
I really am happy…
Карасума-сан, here's your birthday gift!
Th-Thanks… Can I open it?
Sure!
We spent a lot of time
picking that out for you.
Yeah. We wanted something
that would look good on you.
We did our best picking it out.
Despite how busy everyone was,
we were able to match our schedules.
Кото-тян's job and my job
just happened to be close.
We ended up making Нана-тян wait
such a long time. I'm sorry about that.
It's fine! I had fun waiting.
You're such a good kid, Нана-тян.
I'm so glad!
Th-Thanks, everyone…
Pardon me. The taxi's here! Let's head out!
Нанами-тян! Do your best!
Нана-тасо!
Okay! I'll do my best! Thank you so much!
Ти-тян! Ти-тян! Do your best!
Ти-сама-тасо!
Oh, right… Thank you very much.
Cold… So cold. Ice cold for life.
You just lose it when you get older.
Yeah. About time to retire as a Титосэ fan.
Thank you very much!
I'm gonna transfer over
to backing Нанами.
Нанами-тян! Do your best!
Yes! I will!
That's so amazing.
All the fans are so passionate.
So this is what you and
the other two have created!
Oh, right… Actually, I'm not sure about that…
Hard work really does
pay off someday, doesn't it?
You really are amazing, Карасума-сан!
Sakuragaoka, you live in Tama,
right? I'll drive you home.
I do! Thank you very much!
So, yeah…
Yeah…
Our hearts connect…
Are you okay?
Sorry. She's so clumsy.
Taru-кун, you're so mean!
But I really am sorry.
No, it's my fa—
I'm so sorry!
Sorry.
You need to watch where you're going.
What's… with me?
Товада
Входящий звонок…
Алло?
Don't give me that, Кудзу-сан.
We have video editing today!
Huh?
You asked me to help you,
so I worked hard to make sure
things went well,
even if you weren't here.
Right…
Could you please show up to work soon?
We don't have enough people
to make the deliveries.
I-I… can show up?
I'm still needed?
Yes, yes. You're needed.
You were CCed on that message, weren't you?
I'll get the regional deliveries done,
but I need you to do the
deliveries within the city.
Oh, I got it. I definitely got it!
Huh? Wait, what are you…
Товада!
Y-Yes?
I was always the one needing something.
But now that you need me,
I know for the first time…
Basically, because you needed
me needing something…
Actually, I have no idea!
R-Right…
What don't you understand?
Ask, and you shall recieve!
I was right all along! Right?
Er, uh… I don't think so, but…
Right, anyway…
More importantly, the delivery…
All right! Leave it to me!
You and I are going to
beat that guy!
The Ghost Kitten Connection
Playing
My hands are already dirty.
That's Годзё-кун's voice…
How funny. He sounds so young.
But that doesn't mean I can stop.
You totally sucked, too, Годзё-кун.
Just about as much as me…
Карасума Годзё
Other Keywords:        Карасума Годзё College    Карасума Годзё 2000ch
Search Results
Карасума Годзё – Wikipedia
Карасума Годзё is a former male voice actor in Japan. Formerly affiliated with Number One Produce. Born in Tokyo.
Карасума Годзё's
Cotton Days
With the charm of being able
to become anyone and anything
"Being able to become anyone and anything."
As charming and fresh as the summer breeze.
I have to change!
Change. I can change. I need to change.
You can change, too.
Do your best! I know you can
become who you want to be!
Liar.
If I could become who I wanted to be,
I wouldn't be who I am right now.
"You can change"…
That makes no sense, and there's no point.
I wonder
why Годзё-кун quit being a voice actor.