Karasuma Chitose
Karsuma Chi
Karasuma Gojo-sama
...cheering on Chitose-chan...
...Gojo-kun, I'm...
...I'll wait forever...
...love you very much...
Number One Produce
10th Anniversary!
Surprisingly, it only takes
a second to get disheartened,
and everyone has their
own reason for quitting.
Reaching the end of your talent,
lack of technique,
timing, relationships with other people,
the pressure, finding new dreams,
or... all of the above.
#11 Wavering Chitose and Determined Gojo
Yep! Got it! Definitely got it!
If you'll excuse me!
Push the button.
Are you sure you should have said that?
You don't have to listen to
everything your boss tells you.
He'll be saying something
else tomorrow, anyway.
Yeah... Bosses really are like that.
Right? I always ignored what
the bosses I hated had to say.
Like Shakujii-san?
He was only my boss for a second!
I'm going to surpass him with this project!
If we can manage to get
this thing to sell, I'll win.
And I can boldly go see Mai Mai-chan!
Don't worry. I have a secret plan.
"Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord" #23 "Voiceless Scream"
Recording Date: X X 2016: 4PM – 9PM
Recording Studio: Delfire Studio A/R/TWO
Director: Sameyama Yota
Character | Cast | Agency | A | B | Cuts | Notes
Yuna | Karasuma Chitose | Number One Produce
Yuzu | Sono Momoka | Voice Enterprise | Note: Available until 10 PM
Nanaka | Shibasaki Kazuha | Iroha Production
Mao | Kugayama Yae | Number One Produce
Ria | Katakura Koto | Number One Produce
Aila | Sakuragaoka Nanami | Number One Produce | Note: Available until 10PM
Good morning, Chi-chan.
Yeah, good morning.
Sorry we're a bit late.
Good morning!
Our last session ran behind schedule.
Coming to work in your school uniform?
What a great agency.
I'm a high school girl, too, you know.
Well, you know, she's still pretty fresh, so...
What?
Well, I mean...
"Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord" #23 "Voiceless Scream"
Recording Date: X X 2016: 4PM – 9PM
Recording Studio: Delfire Studio A/R/TWO
Director: Sameyama Yota
Character | Cast | Agency | A | B | Cuts | Notes
Yuna | Karasuma Chitose | Number One Produce
Yuzu | Sono Momoka | Voice Enterprise | Note: Available until 10 PM
Nanaka | Shibasaki Kazuha | Iroha Production
Mao | Kugayama Yae | Number One Produce
Ria | Katakura Koto | Number One Produce
Aila | Sakuragaoka Nanami | Number One Produce | Note: Available until 10PM
What's with that face?
Hey!
I'll do my absolute best.
Thank you for having me.
Happy to work with you!
Chitose, is something wrong?
I guess I'm still tired from the last event.
You're at work.
Straighten up.
Oh, thanks...
Looks like you're finally a part of
the Kusure family now, Nana-chan.
Yes! I'll do my best as the youngest sister!
The youngest sister, huh?
It's almost like you're Cinderella.
Your head is full of fairy tales, Yaepon.
Even though you're dark inside.
I'm not dark!
Really?
I-Is that true?
No!
Oh, come on. You're pitch black!
Listen to me!
All right, let's start recording!
But before that...
Nanami-chan, let's run a character check.
Yes! I'll work hard like my life depends on it!
ODD Production
Harukaze Pictures
DDD Production
U-Um, Shibasaki-san...
What did you think of my acting?
I thought it was fine...
You should really ask the sound
director about that, not me.
Oh, but according to the original work,
Aila has more interactions
with Nanaka coming up...
Not to mention, I've always
thought your acting
was wonderful, Shibasaki-san.
I-I see...
Aila
Nana-chan's amazing.
Yeah...
Everyone's so enthusiastic.
It feels like our series is
finally getting exciting.
Yeah. And I guess Nanami
likes this anime, too.
I wonder if girls like her become popular.
But I think that's all because
you're here, Chi-chan.
You think so?
Yeah! Nana-chan's a fan of yours,
and so am I!
So, um...
I think you're working really hard, Chi-chan!
Thanks. You seem to be working
really hard, too, Yae.
All right, we got that one.
One moment, please.
How was that, Director?
Well...
Doesn't it seem a bit heavy in here today?
The mood feels kinda tense, or maybe prickly...
You sure it's not the looks
you're getting that feel prickly?
Why, you little...
Is there anything else?
May I have a moment?
Nanami-chan's absolutely
wonderful, isn't she?
Pardon?
Anyway, I'll go tell them
about the retakes.
Nanami-chan's doing well
with the original series staff.
I think it was a great idea to cast her.
Yeah, that. I guess I've nurtured another one.
Say, Gojo-chan...
How's it going with Seven Seas?
Is her schedule pretty open?
S-Sev... Oh, you mean Nanami?
Since she's a newbie,
that shouldn't be a problem.
I see, I see.
Towada! I think there's a huge issue
with our current sales promotion.
Huh?
I have a secret plan!
Um...
Now, now, I just need you to
let me discuss this with you again later.
Book one of the shops and get in
as many handout events as you can.
We'll reserve Nanami-chan's
schedule for life,
so do the venue booking
as soon as you can.
U-Uh... Is that even okay?
Wow! That's a pretty good song.
It would sound great live.
Nanami-san, you're a very good singer.
Oh, but it's still just a demo...
You did great at your debut
event the other day, too.
Th-That's not true...
Oh, Chi-chan. Do you want
to go to dinner with us?
Let's go! I would love to hear
all of your stories, Karasuma-san.
It'll be a welcome party for her, too.
Though it's already the
eleventh episode of this cour.
Sorry. I'm gonna head home.
Do you have to work early tomorrow?
Um... Yeah. Something like that.
U-Um...
I-I really think...
that Chi-chan is doing her best.
Her acting's gotten much better,
and she's always helping me out at events.
If you don't mind, could you
tell her that directly?
No...
That won't work.
Because my words are cheap...
But I think Chi-chan would actually listen
if it came from you, Karasuma-san.
You do, huh?
Yes!
Um... It may not be my place to say this,
but please take care of Chi-chan!
I wanted to confirm my schedule
before I go to dinner.
Oh, right.
Tomorrow, you have a recording for a game...
You two really are siblings.
She's makin' the same face you did
when you said you were quitting.
That was a long time ago.
Oh, come on. You're the only colleague
I've got left who started
around the same time as me.
You mean former colleague.
I guess.
I really liked your acting, though.
I was totally thinking, "Oh, no.
I'm gonna end up quitting first."
Not to mention, a lot happened.
As soon as I started getting work,
the manager who took care of me quit,
and the structure of the agency changed.
And younger, more talented
girls started showing up.
But...
I'm thankful that I was able
to get another great manager.
Well, see ya, Gojo-san.
It feels strange that Karasuma-san isn't here.
It was always a given that she'd be around.
Chitose, huh...
She's so easy to read.
It's more than obvious
that something happened.
Something like this has happened before, too.
Yeah. She actually talked
to me about it the last time.
And yet this time...
Aha, so that's why you're
in a bad mood, Momocchi.
No! I'm pissed at the fact that Chitose's
regressing rather than progressing.
Um... Did something happen to Karasuma-san?
She's probably just sick of work.
Huh?
That can't be! But she was working today...
That was her just getting through.
You can tell by looking at Chitose's face.
I've seen that same expression a lot of times
on someone else's face until recently.
I saw it so much that I got sick of it, too.
Just because you have talent doesn't
mean things will always go your way.
I've seen lots of colleagues who started
when I did go through the same thing.
Karasuma-san won't quit, will she?
I wonder what's going to happen
at next week's recording...
There's not a chance that
she won't show up, is there?
Huh? Huh? Huh?!
Chi-sama's sort of unpredictable, so...
Though that's why she's fun.
Honestly, she's so erratic,
if not just plain useless.
Her personal motivation
directly affects her work.
She lacks awareness
that she's a professional.
She also lacks talent.
Ch-Chi-chan...
It's not that Chi-chan isn't motivated to work
or has no awareness that she's a professional.
U-Um... She's just...
a little dumb...
Um... I didn't mean that kind of dumb!
She's just sort of innocent!
Or like, innocently dumb!
President!
Nanami-chan's great!
You think so?
Yeah, yeah.
She's the center of attention,
and she just keeps getting bigger.
I think she's just about ready to harvest!
Um... By "secret plan,"
you didn't mean that
you were going to change
the main focus of the promotion
to Nanami-chan, did you?
Well, yeah. Users nowadays are pretty fickle,
so they gradually, often, almost always,
switch up their tastes.
I'm sure it'll be a great experience
for Nanami-chan, too.
I'd like her to gain more experience.
Right?
But it's not just about standing on stage.
Voice actors
watch others act from behind them.
Watching those backs is also
a vital part of being a newbie.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, that. That. I totally understand.
U-Uh...
And...
Having someone watch you
from behind is also experience.
There are those who completely
transform from that.
Transform?
Yep! Well, there are those who
come back to haunt you, too.
Transform, huh...
And the dumber they are,
the better they transform.
That's why I feel like
making a bet on Chitose-kun.
Well, then, why don't we just
go ahead and bet on Chi-sama?
That seems like it'd be an expensive wager.
I guess you could say that she's dumb.
She's almost like an animal living
with the flow and momentum.
On top of that, she gets depressed easily.
She's definitely a naïve girl.
And she can be pretty nasty.
She made it so awkward today.
Oh, I see.
So Karasuma-san is a mood maker.
Well, you're not totally wrong.
So that means...
Karasuma-san is an amazing actress!
You really like Chitose, don't you?
That's rare.
Uh, "rare"?
Karasuma-san is really amazing!
Even with Kusure,
her conversations with Kaito
were awkward at first,
but as the series went on,
they sounded so much closer.
I could tell that she was
growing with her character.
That just means that she was
awful in the beginning.
And she's more energetic and free
than anyone else on the stage.
Well, if nothing else, she definitely has guts.
Thinking about her portraying
the character that I love so much
made me love the character even more.
Though Chi-sama herself is less and less
appealing the more you get to know her.
That's why I really love Karasuma-san.
Me, too.
I really love Chi-chan, too.
Right!
Well, there are times when I don't mind
having someone like her around.
One is more than enough.
If there were two of her,
our sessions would be doomed.
You can say that again.
Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
Episode 24
#24 Check Video
It's already tomorrow...
Here are your presents from the other day.
I'll leave them here.
I wonder how long people
are going to cheer me on.
My next role isn't big, either.
As soon as the show is over,
they'll forget all about me.
I'd be better off if they called me
the voice actress who vanished,
a one-hit-wonder,
or disposable...
But I don't think I'd even fit that description.
You've got plenty of people backing you.
Your fans, the producers, the staff,
are all watching you.
They're all going to forget about me soon!
There are plenty of people who are
cuter or more amazing than me!
They're only keeping their eyes
on me because I'm new!
So what happens when I'm not new anymore?
No one's going to watch me anymore.
I can't work harder for everyone...
I know that's self-complacent...
That I'm too proud and that
I have a lousy personality...
That I just want people
to pay attention to me...
But I can't help it...
Because I want to continue liking myself!
I want other people to keep liking me!
I don't want to disappear.
I don't want to lose to anyone...
I want people to fuss over me.
I want to be number one.
I can't stand to be bashed or left out.
I don't want that...
You really are dumb.
You're definitely meant to be an actress.
I don't need that kind of consolation.
Let me rephrase it, then.
Being an actress is just about
all you can do with that
trash personality of yours.
Huh?
You're stupid, selfish...
You get depressed easily,
but you get a big head even faster.
You're vain, and a huge liar.
You also lack technique, and you're naïve.
You also lack awareness.
You're lazy, and you're way
too proud of your half-ass talent.
And yet,
no one stands a chance against your positive
determination toward everything.
That's something that I didn't have.
Chitose, you're amazing.
This is right around the time that I gave up.
But you've got people who
want to keep cheering you on.
Chitose, you're amazing.
Say it more.
You're amazing.
More!
You're amazing. You really are something.
Be more specific.
Speci—
U-Um, well, as for what exactly
is amazing about you...
I mean, your amazing aspects are amazing.
So, you know... You're amazing.
What's that supposed to mean?
Gojo-kun, you suck at giving compliments.
But I got it.
There's something wrong with this business if
someone as amazing as me doesn't get popular.
Huh?
So I'm going to work hard to become popular.
I want to work hard for my own sake.
Due to the massive cold wave in Tokyo,
all forms of public transportation
have been impacted.
Operations Suspended
Many Lines in the Metropolitan Area are Delayed
Currently, all lines have
been postponed or delayed.
Many highways are also at a standstill.
Preview
The recording session for the
final episode is about to begin.
Will everything go okay?
We're sort of pushing it already...
Oh, everything will be fine.
We'll just leave everything to Chi-sama.
I decided that I was going to bet on her.
Er, I'm not sure if saying that with
a cool expression and voice helps...
Oh, come on. If we showed any anxiety,
it'd make everyone else nervous.
Producers need to act big!
Karasuma Chitose's going to win big!
Ready to go into the future
filled with hope! We won!
Uh...
Come on, repeat after me. We won!