Both directions are experiencing delays because of the snow...
To Shinjuku/Shibuya
Matsuoka
Talking
Do your best to get here!
Apparently, the trains are delayed.
I might not be able to make it...
Do your best to get here!
There is, indeed, a possibility
that I'm going to be late.
Do your best to get here!
I do have every intention
of getting there if I can.
This will probably cause the
dubbing session to start late,
or worst case, to have to be canceled.
They could even do it without
me and get by just fine.
I can't help it if I'm late.
It's not like this is my fault.
Not to mention, I sort of ruined
the mood at the last session.
Actually, it might be
better for everyone else
if I don't go, or something...
It's sort of... awkward
seeing everyone, anyway.
Notification     Gojo-kun
Hurry it up or I'll kill you
OCG Production
Fuyukaze Production
DDD Production
#12 Karasuma Chitose and...
Good morning!
Good morning.
You're early, Shibasaki.
The snow didn't affect you at all?
I wouldn't actually consider this snow.
There you go with that baloney again.
That ain't no baloney.
Karasuma-san is late...
Well, with all this snow,
the trains might've stopped.
They're already running again.
Chi-chan doesn't have anything
on her schedule before this...
I think.
We're waiting for you.
Read
Hurry!!
Whoosh
Read
Hey, Shibasaki, do you remember
the first time you played a heroine?
Like I'd ever forget.
Right? Of course you could never
forget something so awful.
Having people talk behind my back,
having pretentious conversations,
being all alone in a booth
with everyone else there...
Yet I still went every week.
Well, that's sorta surprising.
I didn't think any of that stuff
bothered you, Kazuha-sama.
I don't think anyone's okay with that,
other than maybe Chitose.
I don't think Chi-chan is
actually okay with it, either.
Chi-sama is always really worried
about what people think of her.
Karasuma-san will show up, right?
Well, it's Chi-chan.
Yeah, it's Chitose.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Huh?
This isn't good. This isn't good!
If the dubbing session gets axed, the
episode's broadcast might get axed, too.
Your head's going to get axed, too.
Can't we set another date
for the ones who can't come?
It's only ten days until the broadcast.
If we don't do the dubbing now,
we won't make it in time.
Right...
You think we could do a
recap episode right now?
For the last episode? Of course not.
Well, you know, that might actually
become a legend in and of itself.
That would only be allowed for a major title.
This series is—
I'll go see what's going on.
You work on adjusting the delivery day, please.
Series that end up with
recap episodes are blessed.
Because that means it's being made by
a staff that refuses to compromise on quality.
Only those who haven't done a
half-assed job and managed to deliver
a final product may cast the first stone.
Sensei, please get a hold of yourself.
Hello, hello?
How long do you think you
can wait for the delivery?
You can't? I see...
Then how about a recap epi— No?
Then how about we gloss over it
with a voice actor special?
If you're going to postpone the broadcast,
postpone the release of the original work, too.
Sensei, we can't do that!
Wake up!
No special, either? I see...
Sensei, get a hold of yourself!
Huh? Penalty for breaking
the contract? Huh? Why?!
Just for reference, merely for reference,
how many tens of thousands of yen would...
Leave it to me.
I'll make sure it's done on time.
Gojo-san! I still can't get
a hold of Karasuma-san!
Mattsu, I forgot to mention this.
It's part of the job as Chitose's manager
to be at Chitose's mercy.
So passionate! Nothing less
from you, Gojo-san!
G-G-G-G-G-Gojo-chan!
What's going on with Chi-sama?!
Is it gonna be okay?
Is she coming for sure?
She is, right? Right?!
I'm just going to be me...
Be cute, and slightly annoying...
I wonder if it's like this everywhere...
Good morning!
Oh, um...
You're late!
Don't you have something to say?
Uh... Yeah.
So, um...
It's the red one.
Oh, this one.
At first, I wasn't thinking about anything.
I just did my job like it'd always
be there, and that was normal.
But I was wrong.
It's not like I have a unique voice, and honestly,
there are plenty of girls
who could replace me.
So I couldn't help but think that Momoka-chan
or Kazuha-chan could have done this role.
Why was it me?
Er... I mean, I obviously know it's
because I have such an open schedule,
can work events, and I'm free to use.
It could have been any newbie.
It could have been Yae or Koto-chan...
But before I knew it, there was
a huge gap between us.
I mean, I know it's all because
I'm not that good, but...
So even if I'm not here,
someone can easily take my place.
And that's not anyone's fault or anything...
No, it's my own fault, the fault
of the people who chose me,
the fault of the people who didn't stop me,
and basically, the fault of this whole industry...
And in that case, I thought that I might
be disposable and just disappear...
That it can't be helped...
But even then, this series... I...
To be honest,
I don't really understand this series,
but I'll do my absolute best
so I can become popular.
And if this series sells as
a result, it's win-win!
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll do my best!
That idiot.
Why are you stating the obvious?
I've already felt that way for a long time.
Er... I have no idea how you feel, Momoka-chan.
And I wasn't really asking.
Seriously, what's your problem?!
Now, now...
It's about time.
We're all here because we're trying to
express ourselves as well as the series.
That's our Kazuha-chan. You're so
self-aware. I don't get it at all!
Chi-chan.
Yae...
Thanks.
Yeah.
Karasuma-san, you really are the best.
You always were and always
will be the person I look up to.
I'll keep doing my best to do my best.
Nanami.
Yes, I'll do my best.
You don't have to do your best, Nanami.
Not... do my... best?
Just watch everything that I do!
S-So cool!
All right, Leader,
say something good to get
everyone back on track.
Koto-chan...
Er... The leader should be referring
to the lead role, but...
Let's just relax and sell this thing!
That's what I've been waiting to hear!
I swear, what kind of voice actress is she?
I never want to use her again.
Let's make Nanami-chan the next lead...
Yes?
After the dubbing session is over,
can I use a meeting room?
Huh? Sure, of course...
I feel like writing...
I'm sure there are also a lot of
light novel authors who can replace me...
But still, I want to write.
S-Sensei... That's... That's...
what I've been waiting to hear.
Pyah!
This might not make it in.
Even though the acting was great...
What should we do?
Let's change the drawings.
But we have less than ten days left!
Let's do our best.
I'll go make the calls.
Thanks for waiting.
We have the drawings,
but they're going to change.
I see.
Well, stuff like this always
happens on legendary series.
So it'll happen with this series, too?
Fate's working backwards!
You can't let something like
changing drawings surprise you.
I mean, we've never seen
any decent drawings, anyway.
At first, I barely even saw any decent acting.
Once the cue lamp goes on, please come in
whenever you're ready, Karasuma-san.
Right!
All right, here we go.
You're not even that strong.
What do you think you're doing?
You idiot!
But we can't give up. We can't
let something like this happen!
I was letting the pressure get to me.
I was looking at others for answers.
I was thinking of excuses!
Laughing and saying everything
is fine, that it's not hard...
Of course that's not true!
Even if we're weak, sneaky, or underhanded,
we have to keep struggling until the end!
And the fact that this world was
saved by such a helpless girl...
I'll laugh at this world for
being less than trash!
Because you love this world.
Okay, we got it!
Let's go, Director.
Yeah.
Sensei.
There isn't much that I can do,
but at least I can pray.
Let's write the bonus novel
for the Blu-ray release!
God is dead...
Towada.
Yes?
We've got work to do.
Time to go make apologies.
Right!
Thanks for your hard work.
Girlish Number
In Use
80 Minutes Remaining
There are no further reservations
Reserve
Extend
Leave Room
Animate handout events (Planned for 1/14-1/15, 2/4-2/5)
We are planning handout events with the cast for customers who preorder the
"Kusure" 2nd season package at the Ikebukuro and Akihabara locations of Animate!
Those who preorder also get a newly drawn postcard by Shishida Neru!
Gamers handout events (Planned for 1/14-1/15, 2/4-2/5)
We are planning handout events with the cast for customers who preorder the
"Kusure" 2nd season package at the Akihabara Gamers!
Those who preorder also get a newly drawn postcard by Shishida Neru!
Soft Area handout events (Planned for 1/14-1/15, 1/21-1/22)
We are planning handout events with the cast for customers who preorder the
"Kusure" 2nd season package at Soft Area! (Currently finding participating locations)
Those who preorder also get a newly drawn postcard by Shishida Neru!
Nakanoana handout events
We are planning handout events with the cast for customers who preorder the
"Kusure" 2nd season package at Nakanoana! (Currently finding participating locations)
Those who preorder also get a newly drawn postcard by Shishida Neru!
A&G&K Radio: Be a guest on "Kugayama Yae's Kugayama Mountain-Climbing Plan" (Recording date planned for 1/22)
Be a guest on the radio program "Sakuragaoka Nanami's Nanamen"!!
It's going to be rough, but this is the
only way we can do our best right now!
Um... This is hard for me to say...
Kusure Shop Sales Promotion Event Estimate
Title: Millennium Princess x Kowloon Overlord
Product and Event Name: Second Season Volume 1 Shop Sales Promotion Event
Order Details: Animate, Gamers, etc. Shop Handout Events
Cast Request Below
<Number One Produce> Karasuma Chitose-sama, Kugayama Yae-sama, Katakura Koto-sama, Sakuragaoka Nanami-sama
<Iroha Production> Shibasaki Kazuha-sama
<Voice Enterprise> Sono Momoka-sama
Order Estimate Details
Item  |  Cost (*1)  |  Amount  |  Subtotal
Kusure Shop Sales Promotion Event (Gross) *2
Total
Notes
*1 Amount ordered is not frequency, but gross amount ordered. Monetary amount negotiable.
*2 We are aware that cast members may have scheduling conflicts, so please discuss
which cast members can make which events. Please let us discuss the details gradually.
Please confirm all of the details above. Thank you very much. -Peitax Corportation
But we're estimating the pay to be about this much.
This isn't too bad for a single appearance.
We were thinking that this
would be the gross amount...
Then it's going to be up to Momoka for us.
Huh? But this amount is...
I know, but...
It appears that she really likes this job.
I-I'll at least ask...
Really?!
Yes! We won!
I just said I would ask...
We're fine with that. We're not very busy.
Especially Chitose.
Considering how much the pay is,
you're free to decline.
Um... If you don't want to...
I don't see the harm in helping out
if our schedules are free. Right?
Well, if that's all they need us to do...
Reception Room
I'm fine with this.
Actually, I would love to do this.
I'll do my best!
Chitose, yours is going to be
tight, but can you do it?
Heck yeah!
"On the Way to Tomorrow"
Stealth marketing, des-ma, death march.
Working comes first for a newbie voice actor,
and acting comes second.
Chitose, that's not how the new song goes.
Practice properly.
Yeah.
If you're going to sleep, sleep in your bed.
You worked hard.
Yeah.
I have to get up early tomorrow,
so I'll see you at the venue.
Yeah.
[Performance Date]
2/12/2017 (Sun)
Doors open: 17:00/Performance: 18:00
Cast members, please show up at 13:00, including makeup time.
*We're planning a light rehearsal at 15:00 that day.
There we go.
[Performance Date]
2/12/2017 (Sun)
Doors open: 17:00/Performance: 18:00
Cast members, please show up at 13:00, including makeup time.
*We're planning a light rehearsal at 15:00 that day.
Pyah!
Yes?
Gojo-kun, I'm in trouble!
Like, major trouble! Serious trouble!
I knew it. You idiot...
How many times did I tell
you to prepare properly?
No, no! That's not it!
The other day, it was because of the snow...
Today, it's because the stocks went down!
It's because the economy's bad!
Everything is the fault of politics!
So it's not my fault! It's society's fault!
The Yamanote Line is currently
experiencing some delays.
You're kidding...
You brat. You just overslept.
Mattsu is heading your way. Meet up with him.
Karasuma-san!
Matsuoka-san! This is bad!
Wait! It's too soon to give up!
This route has a transfer—
This is not good!
Crap, crap, crap!
Towada, I'm not gonna make it in time!
You don't need to hurry. I'll figure it out.
Towada, you've grown so much.
Towada
Talking
No, it's just that you haven't
grown at all, Kuzu-san.
Bye.
Pyah!
This is why you've still got so far go!
Which way is it?
At this rate, maybe we should take a bicycle...
Nice joke. I'm going to run.
Got it! I'll take care of the fee!
Right!
Er... You're supposed to take care
of that anyway, Matsuoka-san.
Chitose
Incoming Call...
Gojo-kun, I'm running there right now.
Do you know where the employee entrance is?
I'll be waiting there.
'Kay.
Which way was the employee entrance?
U-Um... You're Karasuma-san, right?
Hey, it's Chi-chan.
I have arrived!
Kuzu-san!
Chitose Karasuma-chan.
Leave this to me and go!
Right! I guess it doesn't matter
if you're there, Kuzu-san!
Kuzu?
He's Kuzu, the screw-up?
Pyah!
Chitose, there's no time
until the performance.
Go get into makeup, then we have a meeting.
Can you do it?
Who do you think I am?
Yeah, who are you?
You've got some nerve, you damn newbie.
Green Room B
Kusure
Cast & Staff
Karasuma Chitose-sama
Sono Momoka-sama
Shibasaki Kazuha-sama
Kugayama Yae-sama
Katakura Koto-sama
You're late!
Well, it is Chitose...
Thank goodness you made it on time.
You really know how to keep us on our toes.
That's right.
I'm just a damn newbie. No one special.
That's exactly why I can
be Karasuma Chitose!
I've always wanted to try this.
Well, I guess it couldn't hurt.
Sounds good. I guess the one who'll lead us in is...
Chi-chan!
Ready, and...
We've won!
Huh?
Why would you lead us in with that?
Our strong feelings
Let's go, oh!
Oh, let's go!
Will give us the push we need,
so I look for them every day
I put a ribbon
Feeling
Let's Feeling
On my overflowing feelings,
waiting for someone to undo it
What should the mirror of the future
reflect? I thought about it, but...
As we are
Let's reach our hands
Toward the door of dreams
Now, let's go!
Monthly Seiyu  TYPE
Super Special Report
Sono Momoka
Bonus
Sono Momoka Pin-up
Shibasaki Kazuha
Special Report
Kusure 2nd Season Finale
Handout Event
Karasuma Chitose
Kugayama Yae
Katakura Koto
Voice Actor Training School Special
"Basic Strength and Going on a Retreat" Part 1
Great job today!
Once I can drink,
I'd love to go, too!
Nanami
Please invite me again next time!
Hiss!
Ugh, I never want to do that again.
Yep, yep.
That was really bad... Both the shitty
original story and the shitty animation.
Nah, the animation turned around
toward the latter half.
At least the cast and songs were great.
That's what you say when
there's nothing else nice to say.
Well, I can't say I hate
this shitty anime, though.
You're lying again.
Found me out, huh?
But I really do like this series a lot.
I've been waiting to hear those words!
Huzzah! We've been waiting
for you, Great Producer!
We've got a new project. Right, Sensei?
Nice! We can do this!
We've won!